<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto Education on Tooabstractive</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/crypto-education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crypto Education on Tooabstractive</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/crypto-education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top Telegram-Based Bot Airdrops in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/crypto-education/telegram-based-bot-airdrops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/crypto-education/telegram-based-bot-airdrops/</guid>
      <description>Airdrops have become a popular method for distributing free tokens to the crypto community, serving as an effective marketing strategy for new projects.&#xA;Recently, Telegram-based bots have gained traction for hosting these airdrops, allowing users to earn tokens conveniently through the messaging app.&#xA;Here are some of the top Telegram-based bot airdrops that offer unique opportunities to engage with the crypto space:&#xA;Top Telegram-Based Bot Airdrops 1. Hamster Kombat Hamster Kombat is a widely popular Telegram-based game with over 150 million players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamster Kombat: How to Increase Profit per Hour Productively</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/crypto-education/hamster-kombat-and-how-to-increase-profit-per-hour-productively/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/crypto-education/hamster-kombat-and-how-to-increase-profit-per-hour-productively/</guid>
      <description>Hamster Kombat is a Telegram-based play-to-earn game with over 150 million players. It offers an engaging way to earn tokens by tapping to earn, upgrading cards for passive income, and participating in various in-game activities.&#xA;Players who effectively mine tokens and increase their profit per hour (PPH) have a higher chance of claiming the airdrop, which will be launched on the TON blockchain.&#xA;How to Play Hamster Kombat + Update &amp;#x1f4a1; You can join Hamster Kombat Telegram bot HERE: https://t.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9&#43; Hamster Kombat Profitable Cards to Increase Your Profit Per Hour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/crypto-education/hamster-kombat-profitable-cards-to-increase-your-profit-per-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/crypto-education/hamster-kombat-profitable-cards-to-increase-your-profit-per-hour/</guid>
      <description>The Hamster Kombat team made a statement on their Telegram channel and Twitter (X) that the airdrop for those mining Hamster Kombat tokens will depend on the profit per hour and some other activity parameters that they will reveal later, but not the coin balance.&#xA;Note: this does not mean that you should burn all your coin balance in an attempt to increase your profit per hour because you will be left with no coins.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
