<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>[&#34;How-to-Tech&#34;] on Tooabstractive</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/how-to-tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in [&#34;How-to-Tech&#34;] on Tooabstractive</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/how-to-tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Barcode in Word In just few steps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-create-barcode-in-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-create-barcode-in-word/</guid>
      <description>Barcodes are sometimes referred to as QR codes, and it is a graphics with code embedded in it.&#xA;The code in it can represent a link to a website, a Word document, an Excel file, a PowerPoint document, PDF and what have you.&#xA;In this how-to guide, I will show you how to create a Barcode or QR code in Microsoft Word.&#xA;Step 1: Open a Word document&#xA;Step 2: On the tab menu, locate insert tab</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Qr Code for a Page in Microsoft Edge</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-create-qr-code-for-a-page-in-microsoft-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-create-qr-code-for-a-page-in-microsoft-edge/</guid>
      <description>There are just 3 steps to create a QR code for a website or in page in Microsoft Edge.&#xA;Step 1 : Browse any website you like to convert to a QR code.&#xA;Step 2 : On the website, right-click on the page and go to &amp;ldquo;Create QR code for this page&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;Step 3 : Lastly, download or scan the QR code. Apart from creating a QR code for the page you are currently on, you can edit the URL before downloading and put a new URL of your choice and then download to your device or scan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Free Graphic Design Software for Graphics Designers [2022]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/best-free-graphic-design-software-for-graphics-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/best-free-graphic-design-software-for-graphics-designers/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we would be discussing on some free best graphic design software to use for design graphing as a graphic design.&#xA;Free Graphics Design Software Inkscape is an open source vector based illustrator it is a free alternative to Adobe Illustrator and offer great feature which can be used to design simple to complex design.&#xA;Some design ideas can be done on Inkscape are business card design, e-book cover design, design of mandala art with it great flexibility, logo design, icon design and also for website mockup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to add sitemap to your site using netlify plugin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-add-sitemap-to-your-site-using-netlify-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-add-sitemap-to-your-site-using-netlify-plugin/</guid>
      <description>You are done building your website, but you need an automatic way of generating sitemap for your website without having to do much work.&#xA;Here is a simple guide on how to do just that.&#xA;Note.&#xA;Your website has to be built with plain old HTML or any SSG (Static Site Generator) such as Hugo, Gatsby, 11ty etc. and also must be uploaded to Netlify.&#xA;You need to go to your Netlify dashboard Click on the Integrations tab On the integration dashboard, click on the search bar and type &amp;ldquo;sitemap&amp;rdquo; Then, click on enable The sitemap plugin prompt &amp;ldquo;install&amp;rdquo; will appear After clicking the &amp;ldquo;Install&amp;rdquo; button, you will be redirected to the dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>how to know the color of any image on firefox browser easily</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-know-the-color-of-any-image-on-firefox-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-know-the-color-of-any-image-on-firefox-browser/</guid>
      <description>Here is how to use Firefox browser Eyedropper to get the color of any image or text on the web&#xA;Go to your Firefox browser or open any page you would like to get color from Click on the menu bar and then click on more tools Click on Eyedropper Lastly, the eyedropper will appear with the hex code showing below it </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to configure a website netlifyCMS to access the admin page using google account</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-configure-a-website-netlifycms-to-access-the-admin-page-using-google-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-configure-a-website-netlifycms-to-access-the-admin-page-using-google-account/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s mini guide, I will be explaining how to access the admin page of a website e.g., yoursite.com/admin which is configured using netlifyCMS using google account.&#xA;The first thing to do is, make sure that there is an admin folder in the root of your website, which has to contain two files: a config.yml and index.html.&#xA;The important thing which allows Netlify to grant access to the admin page when a user goes to his or her website URL/admin is that you there must be a link that has to be embedded into the index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Coding Apps for Android: Learn and Practice in 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/best-coding-apps-for-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/best-coding-apps-for-android/</guid>
      <description>Here are a list of the best coding apps for beginners to start learning how to code in 2023. These apps will help beginners and even intermediate programmers to learn concepts about programming, build projects and solve problems with programming.&#xA;SoloLearn This program offers interactive lessons in several coding languages, including Python, Java, C, C++, C# and more. It also includes a code editor and a user community to help answer questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>27&#43; Online Tools for College Students to Become Smart and Productive (2023)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/online-tools-for-college-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/online-tools-for-college-students/</guid>
      <description>Every student at some point in college will get overwhelmed due to the difficult task often faced with.&#xA;But this difficulty can be reduced with the advent of technology as there are several online tools and software programs to help students learn more conveniently, make research easier, remove grammatical error from writing,&#xA;scan document in high-definition, make citation, break complex problems down by using mind mapping apps and saving of files on the cloud and accessing them when needed even though a copy of the file stored on a hard drive has be lost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netlify Sitemap Plugin: How to Exclude Certain Pages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/netlify-sitemap-plugin-how-to-exclude-certain-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/netlify-sitemap-plugin-how-to-exclude-certain-pages/</guid>
      <description>In one of the previous post, we discussed how to automatically generate a sitemap for a website (Specifically Static Site) using Netlify sitemap plugin.&#xA;But in this post, we would be looking at how to exclude some certain pages that we don&amp;rsquo;t want to show on the sitemap page, since Google will crawl and index whatever it finds in the sitemap.&#xA;Go to your netlify.toml config file and add the following code to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Computer Science Teach Coding?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/does-computer-science-teach-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/does-computer-science-teach-coding/</guid>
      <description>Yes, computer science often includes teaching coding as a core part of the discipline.&#xA;Coding involves writing instructions in a programming language to control the operation of a computer, and is an important tool for solving computer problems and creating software, applications, and systems.&#xA;However, the focus of computer science education can vary, with some programs emphasizing on software and others emphasizing on theoretical computer science, algorithms, data structures, and other areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Programming Languages are Taught in Computer Science?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-programming-languages-are-taught-in-computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-programming-languages-are-taught-in-computer-science/</guid>
      <description>The specific programming languages taught can vary depending on the institution, the course level (e.g., introductory, intermediate, advanced), and the focus of the course (e.g., web development, data science, game development, etc.).&#xA;In addition to learning specific programming languages, computer science courses typically teach fundamental concepts of computer science such as algorithms, data structures, and software development methodologies.&#xA;These concepts can be applied to many programming languages, making them valuable skills for a computer science graduate, regardless of the specific language(s) they learned in their studies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Record Video or Audio without Background Noise</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-record-video-or-audio-without-background-noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-record-video-or-audio-without-background-noise/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to record a video or an audio, but your environment is noisy, and you have nothing to do but to record the video so when you turn up to watch the video or listen to the audio,&#xA;It turns out that it is noisy beyond acceptance after ward you hop up to google and type how to remove noise from video or an audio?&#xA;No worries, you are a few steps away from removing noise from your file and making it sound as if it was recorded in a professional studio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to remove plugins from Netlify?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-plugins-from-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-plugins-from-netlify/</guid>
      <description>In one of our previous post, we discussed on how to install plugins on Netlify.&#xA;But in this post, we are going to be looking at how to remove plugins from Netlify.&#xA;Plugins might be very important because it helps to automate task like generating sitemap for a website or minifying of CSS, JS, or HTML files but with its advantage, it also has downside.&#xA;Because plugins, do increase the build time for deploying a site or even does the opposite of making a site fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fix “Uncaught SyntaxError: import declarations may only appear at top level of a module” | Javascript</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-uncaught-syntaxerror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-uncaught-syntaxerror/</guid>
      <description>The first time I tried to use import * as Math from &amp;quot;./math.js&amp;quot;;&#xA;I got an error saying “Uncaught SyntaxError: import declarations may only appear at top level of a module”&#xA;I tried solving the issue by adding type=&amp;quot;module” to the HTML script tag.&#xA;&amp;lt;script src=&amp;#34;/js/script.js&amp;#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; // is changed to &amp;lt;script src=&amp;#34;/js/script.js&amp;#34; type=&amp;#34;module&amp;#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; Which should work in most cases. Make sure to use “./”, “../” or “/” to kind of help in locating where the file exists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Steps on How to Get Youtube Video Data in JSON Format</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-get-youtube-video-data-in-json-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-get-youtube-video-data-in-json-format/</guid>
      <description>To get your YouTube video data such as link, title in JSON format, here are the steps to follow&#xA;Go to RSS-to-JSON Online converter&#xA;Go to your YouTube channel and grab your channel ID To grab your ID you need to go to your YouTube channel and on the URL of your YouTube page, you will see some code after the https://www.youtube.com/channel/which in my case is UCm814ttdg5c0GvOrRCUE3z8gthat&amp;rsquo;s your channel ID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fix &#34;No utility classes were detected in your source files&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/no-utility-classes-were-detected-in-your-source-files-fixed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/no-utility-classes-were-detected-in-your-source-files-fixed/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I am going to highlight how to troubleshoot “No utility classes were detected in your source files” error in tailwindcss.&#xA;The problem comes most time due to file path not configured properly. So if you don&amp;rsquo;t have a tailwindcss config file in your project, then that might be one of the issue.&#xA;To make a tailwindcss config file, you need to run this command -&#xA;npx tailwindcss init A tailwind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of Google Chrome Useful Keyboard Shortcut Keys (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/list-of-chrome-keyboard-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/list-of-chrome-keyboard-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>Google Chrome keyboard shortcuts offer several benefits that can improve your browsing experience.&#xA;They allow you to complete tasks faster, reducing time spent on the computer and increasing productivity.&#xA;By reducing the need for repetitive mouse movements, keyboards can also reduce hand and wrist strain, especially for those who spend long periods of time in front of a computer.&#xA;In addition, keyboard shortcuts can improve usability for users with disabilities or mobility impairments by making it easier to navigate the site and use content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailwind CSS: how do you add :before and :after pseudo-element?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-add-before-and-after-pseudo-tailwind-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-add-before-and-after-pseudo-tailwind-css/</guid>
      <description>Tailwind CSS is a nice way to write CSS without having to leave your HTML file, which makes it good for large projects.&#xA;But one of it downside is that you need to be good at CSS to use it.&#xA;In this article, we are going to be looking at how to add the :before and :after pseudo-element to an HTML element.&#xA;Know that :before and ::before is the same, the only difference is that the former (:before or :after) is the old version while the later (::before or ::after) is used in CSS3 – the new version to separate pseudo-elements from pseudo-classes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Vite with React? Learn How to Create React App with Vite</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-use-vite-with-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-use-vite-with-react/</guid>
      <description>Vite is a popular build tool among developers which offers fast development and reduced build times.&#xA;It is packed with features like instant server start, hot module reload (HMR) and pre-bundling.&#xA;Why should you use Vite to Create React App (CRA)? If you have ever used the normal create react app offered by the developers of React, you will see that it takes time to create a React app even though you just want to use it for a simple project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Import and Export Modules in Javascript | Simple Explanation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-export-and-import-modules-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-export-and-import-modules-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>What is and Why use Module?&#xA;A module in simple term is a broken piece from a huge file. Or let say you have several files and instead of jamming everything into a single js file you can split it into several js files and import each file where necessary.&#xA;It makes code easier to manage and also to help abstract some stuff so you would just focus on executing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Preview Markdown(.md) File in VSCode</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-preview-markdown-md-file-in-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-preview-markdown-md-file-in-vscode/</guid>
      <description>Markdown is a simple and lightweight markup language that is easy to learn and versatile, making it a popular choice among developers for creating formatted documents, notes, and documentation.&#xA;It can be easily managed with version control systems, integrated with other tools and platforms, and helps maintain consistency in formatting. A markdown file ends with (.md) extension.&#xA;Steps on How to Preview Markdown(.md) File in Visual Studio Code To preview Markdown files in Visual Studio Code (VSCode), here are the steps you can follow:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Javascript ES6 (ECMAScript 6) Explained for Beginners</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/explain-es6-in-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/explain-es6-in-detail/</guid>
      <description>ES6, or ECMAScript 6, is a version of JavaScript that comes with several new features and improvements to the language.&#xA;Here are some of the key features of ES6 explained for beginners:&#xA;1. let and const keywords: let and const are two new ways to declare variables in JavaScript. Variables declared with let are block-scoped, meaning they are only accessible within the block they are declared in, and can be reassigned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTML “textarea” Required Attribute Not Working | How to Fix?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/html-textarea-required-attribute-not-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/html-textarea-required-attribute-not-working/</guid>
      <description>To make an HTML form “textarea” to have a required attribute, all you need to do is to add required or required=&amp;quot;required&amp;quot;&#xA;But sometimes when you add the required attribute to force the user to input data, it does not work. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to fix it.&#xA;Make sure that the &amp;lt;textarea&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/textarea&amp;gt; does not have space in between because if it does have then you have already input some character or text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Hexagonal Shape Is Preferred in Cellular Architecture?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/why-hexagonal-shape-is-preferred-in-cellular-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/why-hexagonal-shape-is-preferred-in-cellular-architecture/</guid>
      <description>A cellular land area in cellular networks refers to the geographical area that is divided into smaller regions, or cells, each of which is served by a mobile phone base station.&#xA;The size and shape of the cells depend on factors such as the number of users in the area, the terrain, and the availability of resources.&#xA;The hexagonal shape is preferred in cellular architecture because, it allows for complete and balanced coverage with minimal overlap, which reduces the number of base stations required to cover an area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 Essential Tools Engineering Students Need the Most</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/essential-tools-do-engineering-students-need/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/essential-tools-do-engineering-students-need/</guid>
      <description>Here are 12 essential tools every engineering student must have. The purpose of these tools is to help engineering student succeed in their coursework and career, have a nice time studying and be productive.&#xA;1/ Scientific Calculator A scientific calculator is a must-have for any engineering student. It is used to perform complex mathematical calculations, including logarithms, trigonometric functions, and exponential functions.&#xA;These functions can be challenging to calculate manually, so a scientific calculator can make the process much easier, accurate and time -saving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Does ChatGPT Get Its Data From?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/where-does-chatgpt-get-data-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/where-does-chatgpt-get-data-from/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence (AI) has revolutionized various aspects of our lives, and one of its notable advancements is the development of conversational AI chatbots like ChatGPT.&#xA;These chatbots have become increasingly sophisticated, capable of generating human-like responses to user inputs.&#xA;But have you ever wondered where ChatGPT gets its data from to provide such insightful and contextually relevant answers?&#xA;In this article, we will delve into the data sources that fuel ChatGPT&amp;rsquo;s knowledge and explore the methods employed to ensure its accuracy and reliability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Are the Advantages and Disadvantages of Electronic Payments System?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-are-the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-electronic-payments-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-are-the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-electronic-payments-system/</guid>
      <description>An electronic payment system is a way of making financial transactions through electronic channels, such as the internet, mobile devices, or other electronic means. It allows individuals, businesses, and organizations to transfer money, pay bills, purchase goods and services, and conduct other financial transactions without the need for physical cash or checks.&#xA;Electronic payment systems typically involve the use of payment cards, digital wallets, bank transfers, and other electronic payment methods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advantages and Disadvantages of Digital Systems</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/advantages-and-disadvantages-of-digital-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/advantages-and-disadvantages-of-digital-system/</guid>
      <description>Digital systems are computer-based systems that are used to process and store information.&#xA;These systems can be used for a variety of purposes, including communication, data storage, and automation of tasks.&#xA;What are the Advantages and Disadvantages of Digital System? Advantages of digital systems: Digital systems are fast and efficient, which means that they can process information and perform tasks much faster than manual systems, which can improve productivity and reduce waiting times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between Dev-Dependency and Dependency?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-dev-dependency-and-dependency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-dev-dependency-and-dependency/</guid>
      <description>Dependency and devDependency are external packages or libraries that a project or application relies on in order to function or execute properly.&#xA;The difference between a dependency and a devDependency is that dependency is needed always both in development and production phase, while devDependency is needed only in the development phase.&#xA;What is Dependency and DevDependency? Dependency is a package that is required for an application to function, and it is needed in the development process as well as in the production process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Is the Best Place To Put an HTML Script Tag?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/where-is-the-best-place-to-put-the-script-tag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/where-is-the-best-place-to-put-the-script-tag/</guid>
      <description>An HTML script tag &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; ..... &amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; can be placed in the head section &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; .. &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; or at the bottom of an HTML document – which is just before the closing of the body tag &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; ... &amp;lt;/body&amp;gt;.&#xA;&amp;lt;!DOCTYPE html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;html lang=&amp;#34;en&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Script Tag Placement&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt; &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; // Inline script in the &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; section console.log(&amp;#39;This is an inline script in the &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; section&amp;#39;); &amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Ahoy! Everyone&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This inline script below is place at the bottom of the body section &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; // Inline script in the &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; section just before the body closing tag console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Is Better Yarn or npm?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-is-better-yarn-or-npm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-is-better-yarn-or-npm/</guid>
      <description>Yarn and NPM are package managers that help developers to install, manage, and update the software packages (also known as dependencies and or devDependencies) that their application needs. Applications such as a Node.js, React and Angular application.&#xA;Read on: Difference Between Dev Dependency and Dependency?&#xA;These packages can be libraries like “react”, frameworks such as “express”, or other tools that add functionality to your application.&#xA;Since both Yarn and NPM does almost the same thing, which one is better?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Google Bard Better Than ChatGPT?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-google-bard-better-than-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-google-bard-better-than-chatgpt/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT has set the tech industry ablaze with its unprecedented language processing capabilities.&#xA;It was released to the public in the late November 2022 and in just few months, ChatGPT is able to reach over 100 millions users.&#xA;Read on: Where does ChatGPT get its data from?&#xA;News of its impact at Google has sparked a “code red” situation, prompting the CEO of Google Sundar Pichai to call on the company&amp;rsquo;s founders to re-engage in discussions about AI&amp;rsquo;s future as the tech giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is package-lock.json needed for deployment?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-package-lock-json-needed-for-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-package-lock-json-needed-for-deployment/</guid>
      <description>When working on a Node.js project or any project that need some Node.js dependencies, you will definitely have two JSON files. One of them been package.json and the other package-lock.json.&#xA;The purpose of package.json and package-lock.json in a Node.js project, is to ensure that all the dependencies or packages that are needed for your application to function properly are tracked.&#xA;The main things that are tracked are the names of the packages and their versions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Fix ‘MODULE_NOT_FOUND’ Error in Node.js</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-module-not-found-error-in-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-module-not-found-error-in-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>If you have been working with Node.js for a while, chances are you have encountered the MODULE_NOT_FOUND error at some point.&#xA;This error occurs when you try to require a module in your Node.js code, but the module cannot be found.&#xA;In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore what causes this error and how to fix it.&#xA;What Is the MODULE_NOT_FOUND Error? The MODULE_NOT_FOUND error is a runtime error in Node.js that occurs when you try to require a module that does not exist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Access a File in Node.js? ( /, ./, and ../ ) Paths Explained</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/access-a-file-in-node-js-using-relative-and-absolute-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/access-a-file-in-node-js-using-relative-and-absolute-path/</guid>
      <description>File paths are an essential part of navigating the file system while working on a Node.js project.&#xA;Understanding how to specify file paths using the /, ./, and ../ symbols is important for accessing files and directories.&#xA;When requiring a Node.js module or file, you can specify the file path using a relative or absolute path.&#xA;If the file path begins with ./ or ../, Node.js will interpret it as a relative path, and if it begins with /, Node.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Image Width and Height in Node.js</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-get-image-width-and-height-in-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-get-image-width-and-height-in-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>Most times, when working with images in Node.js, you need to know the size or dimension like the height and width of the image in order to work with it in your code.&#xA;There are several libraries and modules available to help accomplish this task. Two of the most popular and widely used packages are sharp and image-size.&#xA;`sharp` Package sharp is a powerful and efficient image processing library that can be used for a wide range of image manipulation tasks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Uninstall an NPM Package?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-uninstall-an-npm-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-uninstall-an-npm-package/</guid>
      <description>As a developer, you&amp;rsquo;re always on the lookout for new tools and packages that can help you build better software.&#xA;But as your project grows and evolves, you may find yourself with a bloated dependency list that slows down your development process.&#xA;Removing or uninstalling unnecessary packages from your project is an important step in keeping your codebase clean and efficient.&#xA;In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore two ways for uninstalling an npm package from your project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does ChatGPT Use the Internet?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/does-chatgpt-use-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/does-chatgpt-use-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT, the AI language model developed by OpenAI, has gained significant popularity due to its remarkable ability to generate coherent and contextually appropriate responses.&#xA;While it usually performs admirably, it is important to note that ChatGPT may occasionally provide inaccurate information regarding people, places, or facts.&#xA;In this article, we will explore the sources of ChatGPT&amp;rsquo;s data, its limitations, and its relationship with the internet.&#xA;Understanding ChatGPT&amp;rsquo;s Data Acquisition ChatGPT is trained on an extensive dataset of text and code sourced from the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference between GPT-1, GPT-2, GPT-3/3.5 and GPT-4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-gpt-1-gpt-2-gpt-3-gpt-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-gpt-1-gpt-2-gpt-3-gpt-4/</guid>
      <description>GPT is a term that have been used some long time ago in the AI (Artificial Intelligence) field, but it only becomes more popular due to the latest AI conversational chatbot that took the internet by storm! — ChatGPT.&#xA;Read on: Where does ChatGPT get its data from?&#xA;Read on: Does ChatGPT use the internet?&#xA;What is GPT? GPT stands for “Generative Pre-trained Transformer” and it is a type of artificial intelligence (AI) language model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Version of GPT Is ChatGPT Using?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-version-of-gpt-is-chat-gpt-using/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-version-of-gpt-is-chat-gpt-using/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT, developed by OpenAI, is an advanced chatbot designed to provide detailed and knowledgeable responses across various subjects.&#xA;It was introduced as a prototype on November 30, 2022, has quickly gained popularity for its conversational abilities.&#xA;ChatGPT uses the GPT-3.5 model and has recently been updated to incorporate the latest GPT model, GPT-4.&#xA;Read on: Difference between GPT-1, GPT-2, GPT-3/3.5 and GPT-4&#xA;What Version of GPT Is ChatGPT Using? GPT-3.5 and ChatGPT ChatGPT originally utilized the GPT-3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is the Difference Between console.log() and alert() in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console-log-and-alert-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console-log-and-alert-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>console.log() and alert() are functions/methods in JavaScript that are used for displaying messages, but they are used for different purposes.&#xA;Method is just a function inside another function.&#xA;The main difference between console.log() and alert() in JavaScript is that console.log() is part of the console object while alert() is part of the window object.&#xA;What is console.log()? console.log() is used for printing messages or values to the browser&amp;rsquo;s console, which is a developer tool for debugging and troubleshooting code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When To Use Var, Let, and Const in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/when-to-use-var-let-and-const-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/when-to-use-var-let-and-const-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>var, let, and const are all used for declaring variables in JavaScript, but they have some differences in terms of scoping and mutability (i.e., the tendency to change).&#xA;Variable:&#xA;Think of a variable as a labeled storage box where you can put different things, like numbers, words, or even more complex information. You can name the box, store values in it, and later access or modify those values as needed in your code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between console.log() and document.write() in JavaScript</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console.log-and-document.write-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console.log-and-document.write-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>The main difference between console.log() and document.write() is that console.log() outputs information to the browser&amp;rsquo;s console for debugging and testing purposes, while document.write() directly modifies the HTML document, inserting content into the web page visible to users.&#xA;What is console.log()? Console.log() is a method used for debugging and logging purposes in JavaScript. It prints the specified message or value to the browser&amp;rsquo;s console.&#xA;The console is a developer tool included in web browsers like Chrome and Firefox that allows developers to view and interact with JavaScript code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between console.log() and return in JavaScript</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console.log-and-return-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console.log-and-return-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>console.log() is used for printing information to the console during program execution, while return is used to provide a value back to the caller and terminate the execution of a function.&#xA;i.e., console.log() is for logging, while return is for determining the output or result of a function.&#xA;What is console.log() in JavaScript? console.log() is a built-in function that allows developers to print information to the console during the execution of a program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Share or Send Multiple Photos From WhatsApp to Email?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-share-or-send-multiple-photos-from-whatsapp-to-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-share-or-send-multiple-photos-from-whatsapp-to-email/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to share multiple photos from WhatsApp to email? Sharing a bunch of images can be a hassle if you&amp;rsquo;re unsure of the process.&#xA;In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through two ways in which you can use to share multiple photos directly from your WhatsApp chat to an email recipient. We&amp;rsquo;ll also provide additional tips for optimizing the process and troubleshooting common issues.&#xA;By following these steps and implementing the suggestions, you&amp;rsquo;ll streamline the photo-sharing experience and ensure a hassle-free transfer of your cherished memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between map() and filter() in JavaScript With Example</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-map-and-filter-in-javascript-with-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-map-and-filter-in-javascript-with-example/</guid>
      <description>map() and filter() are methods in JavaScript that are used to perform operations on arrays. When the operation or transformation is done, a new array is returned as a result.&#xA;The map method transforms each element of an array and creates a new array with the transformed values, while the filter method creates a new array by selecting only the elements that satisfy a specified condition.&#xA;Difference Between map() and filter() map() Method map method is used to transform an array by applying a function to each element and creating a new array with the transformed values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between forEach and for…in Loop in JavaScript</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-foreach-and-forin-loop-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-foreach-and-forin-loop-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>forEach loop and the for...in loop are two different ways to iterate over elements in JavaScript.&#xA;forEach loop is used to iterate over the elements of an array, whereas the for...in loop is used to iterate over the properties of an object. They have different purposes and are suited for different data structures.&#xA;Difference Between forEach and for…in Loop forEach Loop: forEach loop is a method available for arrays in JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between the ‘This’ and ‘That’ Keyword in JavaScript</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-this-and-that-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-this-and-that-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>this is a keyword in JavaScript that refers to the current execution context or the object that a function is being executed within. It allows you to access and manipulate properties and methods within that context.&#xA;While that is a keyword that is commonly used as a variable that serve as workarounds to preserve the value of this in certain situations, especially when dealing with nested or callback functions, where the value of this might refer to a different object or be undefined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between Normal (Regular) Function and Arrow Function</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-normal-function-and-arrow-function/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-normal-function-and-arrow-function/</guid>
      <description>Functions, in JavaScript, are a fundamental concept that allow us to encapsulate reusable blocks of code.&#xA;Regular functions also known as normal functions and arrow functions are two commonly used function types, each with its own characteristics and use cases.&#xA;In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore these differences in detail, covering their syntaxes, lexical scope (i.e., surrounding scope), “this” binding, the use of “return,”, others and provide code examples to illustrate each concept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the use of underscore ( _ ) in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-use-of-underscore-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-use-of-underscore-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Underscore (_) is just a character that has no special meaning in JavaScript. But it can be used for different purposes.&#xA;Use of underscore (_) in JavaScript Here are some of the uses of underscore in JavaScript:&#xA;1. Variable name spacing The most common use of an underscore in JavaScript is to give space to a variable name, which makes it easier to understand what a variable is all about. For example, var my_variable = 10;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between JavaScript Object and JSON</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-javascript-object-and-json/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-javascript-object-and-json/</guid>
      <description>JavaScript Objects are in-memory data structures that allow direct manipulation and access within JavaScript code. They are versatile, mutable, and provide an object-oriented approach to organizing data.&#xA;JSON, on the other hand, is a text-based data interchange format designed for easy data transmission and interoperability between systems.&#xA;It provides a standardized way to represent structured data as a string, making it suitable for communication between different platforms and programming languages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix WhatsApp Is Not Installing in My Android?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/why-whatsapp-is-not-installing-in-my-android-how-to-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/why-whatsapp-is-not-installing-in-my-android-how-to-fix/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp is a widely utilized messaging application with a global user base of millions. However, sometimes users encounter issues while trying to install WhatsApp on their Android devices.&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re facing similar problems and wondering how to fix the “WhatsApp is not installing in my Android” issue, this article will provide you with effective solutions to overcome this frustrating situation.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Possible Causes of WhatsApp Installation Issues 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Polling on WhatsApp – A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-add-polling-on-whatsapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-add-polling-on-whatsapp/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp is not only a messaging app, but also a platform that offers various interactive features to engage with your contacts. One such feature is the ability to create polls, which allows you to gather opinions and make decisions more efficiently.&#xA;In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process of adding polls on WhatsApp, enabling you to harness the power of polling within your chats.&#xA;How to Add Polling on WhatsApp Step 1 – Launch the WhatsApp App To get started with creating a poll, open the WhatsApp app on your device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differences between ChatGPT and ChatGPT Plus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-chatgpt-and-chatgpt-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-chatgpt-and-chatgpt-plus/</guid>
      <description>In November 2022, OpenAI introduced ChatGPT to the public as a free-of-charge service. However, in early 2023, they also released a pro version called ChatGPT Plus.&#xA;This raises the question: What features and distinctions does ChatGPT Plus offer compared to the free version?&#xA;ChatGPT is a powerful language model that can be used for a variety of tasks, such as generating text, translating languages, and answering your questions in an informative way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Convert a Title to URL Slug in JavaScript</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-convert-a-title-to-url-slug-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-convert-a-title-to-url-slug-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>URLs hold immense significance in web development, as they define the structure and accessibility of web pages. A key aspect of creating user-friendly and SEO-optimized URLs is the utilization of URL slugs.&#xA;This article focuses on the conversion of titles to URL slugs using JavaScript. We will explore various methods, delve into best practices, and examine implementation techniques to effectively accomplish this task.&#xA;What is a URL Slug? A URL slug is the part of a URL that identifies a specific page or resource.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regular Expression in Python: A Step by Step Explanation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-are-regular-expressions-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-are-regular-expressions-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Regular expressions are powerful tools used for pattern matching and manipulating text in various programming languages, including Python.&#xA;In this article, we will explore regular expressions in Python, providing a step-by-step explanation of their usage and syntax.&#xA;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced programmer, this guide will help you grasp the concepts and techniques of regular expressions in Python.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What are Regular Expressions? Basic Syntax of Regular Expressions Creating Regular Expressions in Python Matching Patterns in Python using Regular Expressions Character Classes and Metacharacters Quantifiers and Repetitions Anchors and Boundaries Capturing Groups and Backreferences Lookahead and Lookbehind Assertions Common Use Cases and Practical Examples Best Practices for Using Regular Expressions Troubleshooting and Debugging Advanced Regular Expression Techniques Conclusion FAQs What are Regular Expressions?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Split an Array in 2 Parts in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-split-array-in-2-parts-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-split-array-in-2-parts-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Arrays are a fundamental data structure in JavaScript that allow us to store multiple values in a single variable.&#xA;There are various scenarios where we may need to split an array into two parts.&#xA;In this article, we will explore different methods to achieve this task and understand their pros and cons.&#xA;What is an Array in JavaScript? Before going into splitting arrays, let&amp;rsquo;s quickly review what arrays are in JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Dictionaries: A Beginner&#39;s Guide with Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/python-dictionary-with-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/python-dictionary-with-example/</guid>
      <description>Are you a beginner looking to understand Python dictionaries? In this comprehensive guide, we will walk you through the concept of dictionaries in Python, providing clear explanations and practical examples along the way.&#xA;By the end of this article, you will have a solid understanding of Python dictionaries and how to utilize them effectively in your coding journey.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is a Python Dictionary? Creating a Python Dictionary Accessing Dictionary Values Modifying Dictionary Values Adding and Removing Items Dictionary Methods Iterating Over a Dictionary Dictionary Operations Nested Dictionaries Final Thought What is a Python Dictionary?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the pop() Method in Python? A Comprehensive Guide with Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-pop-in-python-and-how-to-use-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-pop-in-python-and-how-to-use-it/</guid>
      <description>Python is a versatile and powerful programming language that offers a wide range of built-in methods and functions to manipulate data structures. One such method is pop(), which allows us to remove and retrieve elements from lists.&#xA;In this article, we will explore the pop() method in Python, understand its syntax and parameters, and learn how to use it effectively.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Understanding the pop() Method Syntax Parameters Return Value Examples of Using pop() 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between Wi-Fi and Bluetooth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-wifi-and-bluetooth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-wifi-and-bluetooth/</guid>
      <description>Wireless communication has become an integral part of our daily lives, enabling us to connect and share information effortlessly.&#xA;Two prominent wireless technologies that we often encounter are Wi-Fi and Bluetooth. While both serve the purpose of facilitating wireless communication, they differ in various aspects.&#xA;In this article, we will explore the differences between Wi-Fi and Bluetooth, shedding light on their functionalities, advantages, limitations, and use cases.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is Wi-Fi?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference between Wi-Fi and MiFi: All You Need to Know</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-wifi-and-mifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-wifi-and-mifi/</guid>
      <description>Wireless connectivity has revolutionized the way we connect to the internet and interact with the digital world. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s browsing the web, streaming movies, or sharing files, the ability to connect wirelessly has become essential.&#xA;Wi-Fi and MiFi are two popular technologies that enable wireless connectivity, but they serve different purposes and have distinct features.&#xA;In this article, we will explore the intricacies of Wi-Fi and MiFi, comparing their features, functionality, and use cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference between Wi-Fi and Router: Understand the Basics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-wifi-and-router/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-wifi-and-router/</guid>
      <description>Wireless networks have become an integral part of our modern lives, enabling us to connect to the internet seamlessly. While terms like Wi-Fi and router are commonly used, there seems to be confusion regarding their meaning and how they differ from each other.&#xA;In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the details and clarify the distinctions between Wi-Fi and a router, shedding light on their functionalities and roles in creating wireless networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the difference between Wi-Fi and WLAN?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-wi-fi-and-wlan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-wi-fi-and-wlan/</guid>
      <description>Wi-Fi and WLAN are terms that are often used interchangeably, but they have different meanings and applications.&#xA;In this article, we will explore the difference between Wi-Fi and WLAN, understanding their technical and practical aspects.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is Wi-Fi and How it Works? What is WLAN and How it Works? Wi-Fi vs. WLAN: Technical Differences: Wi-Fi vs. WLAN: Practical Differences: Conclusion FAQs What is Wi-Fi and How it Works?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Radio Frequency Identification (RFID) Used For?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-rfid-used-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-rfid-used-for/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, technology continues to play a crucial role in various industries.&#xA;One such technology that has gained significant attention and revolutionized numerous sectors is RFID, or Radio-Frequency Identification.&#xA;RFID offers a wide range of applications across diverse fields, providing improved efficiency, accuracy, and convenience.&#xA;In this article, we will dive into the sphere of RFID and explore its applications and benefits.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is RFID?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Reverse a String in JavaScript: 3 Easy Ways</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-reverse-a-string-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-reverse-a-string-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>In JavaScript, strings are a fundamental data type used to represent text. There may be situations where you need to reverse a string, either for data manipulation or to achieve a specific functionality.&#xA;In this article, we will explore various techniques and methods to reverse a string in JavaScript.&#xA;By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a solid understanding of the different approaches and be able to choose the one that best suits your needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Loop in Python: An Easy Explanation with Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-for-loop-explain-with-example-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-for-loop-explain-with-example-in-python/</guid>
      <description>In the sphere of programming, understanding control structures is vital, and one such structure in Python is the “for loop.” It allows developers to iterate over a sequence of elements effortlessly.&#xA;This article aims to provide a straightforward explanation of the for loop in Python, accompanied by illustrative examples.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is a For Loop? Syntax of a For Loop Code Examples Explaining For Loop in Python Example 1: Basic For Loop Example 2: For Loop with Range Example 3: For Loop with Strings Example 4: Nested For Loop Example 5: For Loop with Break Example 6: For Loop with Continue Example 7: For Loop with Else Final Thought FAQs What is a For Loop?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is a List in Python with Example?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-a-list-in-python-with-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-a-list-in-python-with-example/</guid>
      <description>A list in Python is a mutable, ordered collection of elements enclosed in square brackets ([]). It can store elements of different data types, such as integers, strings, or even other lists.&#xA;Lists are dynamic, meaning they can grow or shrink in size as needed. This flexibility makes lists a powerful tool for various data manipulation tasks.&#xA;With the ability to store multiple items, lists provide an efficient way to organize and access data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstraction in Computer Science Explained (With Examples)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-abstraction-in-computer-science-with-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-abstraction-in-computer-science-with-example/</guid>
      <description>Abstraction is a fundamental concept in computer science that helps simplify complex systems, making them more manageable and easier to understand.&#xA;It allows programmers to focus on essential aspects while hiding intricate details.&#xA;In this article, we will explore the concept of abstraction in computer science, its importance, how it works, and provide real-world examples to illustrate its practical applications.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What Is Abstraction in Computer Science? Why Is Abstraction Important?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between Computer Science and Software Engineering</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-computer-science-and-software-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-computer-science-and-software-engineering/</guid>
      <description>The fields of computer science and software engineering plays significant roles in the ever-evolving technological landscape. While they are closely related, these disciplines have distinct focuses and applications.&#xA;Having a clear understanding of the difference between computer science and software engineering is essential for individuals seeking to pursue careers in these fields or leverage their expertise.&#xA;In this article, we will explore the disparities between computer science and software engineering, digging into their core principles, methodologies, and career prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance vs. Monitoring: What&#39;s The Difference?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-surveillance-and-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-surveillance-and-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>Surveillance and monitoring are closely related terms that are often used interchangeably.&#xA;But, it is important to recognize the differences between these concepts and how they are applied.&#xA;In this article, we will look at the difference between surveillance and monitoring, including their definitions, purposes, durations, intrusiveness, and scopes.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Surveillance (Systematic Information Collection) Monitoring (Ongoing Observation for Specific Purposes) Key Differences: Duration, Intrusiveness, and Scope Surveillance and Monitoring Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) Surveillance (Systematic Information Collection) Surveillance involves the systematic collection of information about a person or a group of people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examples of AI Technology and How They Are Used Today</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-are-examples-of-ai-technology-and-how-is-it-used-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-are-examples-of-ai-technology-and-how-is-it-used-today/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence (AI) has become an integral part of our modern society, transforming the way we live, work, and interact with technology.&#xA;From virtual assistants to self-driving cars, AI technology has revolutionized various industries and continues to shape our future.&#xA;In this article, we will look at several examples of AI technology and dive into how they are utilized in today&amp;rsquo;s world.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;1. Smart Assistants 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech-Driven Strategies for Optimal Medical Billing Performance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/strategies-for-optimal-medical-billing-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/strategies-for-optimal-medical-billing-performance/</guid>
      <description>With the passage of time, many parts of healthcare reform have changed, such as value-based compensation models, the rule engine for medical billing services, and other federal policies.&#xA;Because these changes are always happening, doctors need to know what&amp;rsquo;s new. So, they also need to learn new rules about medical billing and coding all the time.&#xA;Doctors can&amp;rsquo;t lower the quality of their clinical services, or they&amp;rsquo;ll lose money, so they can&amp;rsquo;t stay out of date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between Email and Gmail: A Detailed Comparison</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-email-and-gmail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-email-and-gmail/</guid>
      <description>Email has revolutionized communication in the digital age, providing a convenient and efficient means of sending and receiving electronic messages.&#xA;With numerous email service providers available, Gmail, developed by Google, has emerged as a leading choice.&#xA;This article aims to provide a detailed comparison between email as a general concept and Gmail as a specific email service provider.&#xA;By examining various aspects such as accessibility, features, security, and more, we can understand the unique advantages and disadvantages of both options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming vs. Coding: What&#39;s The Key Difference?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-difference-between-programming-and-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-difference-between-programming-and-coding/</guid>
      <description>The terms “programming” and “coding” are often used interchangeably in the world of technology and software development, leading to confusion among beginners and even some experienced professionals.&#xA;However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand that while programming and coding are related concepts, they have distinct differences.&#xA;This article aims to highlight the differences between programming and coding, clarifying their roles, methodologies, and applications.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Programming Definition of Programming The Scope of Programming Programming Paradigms Coding Definition of Coding The Role of Coding Coding as a Skill Key Differences Between Programming and Coding 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel Core i3, i5, and i7 Processors: What&#39;s The Difference?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-core-i3-i5-i7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-core-i3-i5-i7/</guid>
      <description>The Intel Core i3, i5, and i7 processors are part of Intel&amp;rsquo;s lineup of CPUs designed for desktop and laptop computers.&#xA;These processors come with varying features and capabilities, catering to different levels of computing requirements.&#xA;Understanding their differences will empower you to select the processor that suits your specific needs.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Number of Cores Clock Speed Cache Size Hyperthreading Performance Comparison Choosing the Right Processor Wrap Up FAQs Number of Cores One of the fundamental distinctions between the Intel Core i3, i5, and i7 processors is the number of cores they possess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compiler vs. Interpreter: What&#39;s The Difference?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-compiler-and-interpreter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-compiler-and-interpreter/</guid>
      <description>When programming, developers use high-level programming languages to write human-readable code.&#xA;However, computers understand and execute instructions in low-level machine language.&#xA;This is where compilers and interpreters come into play, as they bridge the gap between human-readable code and machine-executable instructions.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is a Compiler? What is an Interpreter? Compilation Process Interpretation Process Key Differences 1. Approach 2. Execution Speed 3. Error Detection 4. Memory Usage 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between Compiler and Assembler</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-compiler-and-assembler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-compiler-and-assembler/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to translating and converting programming code into machine-executable instructions, both compilers and assemblers play crucial roles.&#xA;While they have similarities, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the key differences between these two tools.&#xA;In this article, we will look at the distinction between compilers and assemblers, highlighting on their functionalities and use cases.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Definition of Compiler Definition of Assembler Compilation Process Assembly Process Key Differences 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Key Difference Between CPU and System Unit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-cpu-and-system-unit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-cpu-and-system-unit/</guid>
      <description>CPU (Central Processing Unit) and the system unit play vital roles in the processing and functioning of a computer system.&#xA;While they are interconnected, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the key differences between these two components.&#xA;This article aims to highlight on the distinction between the CPU and the system unit, exploring their functions, physical structures, and other notable characteristics.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Definition of CPU Definition of System Unit Components of CPU Components of System Unit Key Differences 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSD vs. HDD: What&#39;s The Difference?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-ssd-and-hdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-ssd-and-hdd/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to data storage, two common terms that often come up are SSD and HDD. SSD stands for Solid State Drive, while HDD stands for Hard Disk Drive.&#xA;Both of these technologies serve the purpose of storing your files and data, but they differ significantly in terms of their underlying technology, performance, and reliability.&#xA;In this article, we will look into the details of SSDs and HDDs, explaining the differences between them and helping you make an informed decision about which one is best suited for your needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between console.log and console.error</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console.log-and-console.error/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console.log-and-console.error/</guid>
      <description>In JavaScript programming, developers often use console.log and console.error for debugging and troubleshooting purposes.&#xA;These two functions play a vital role in displaying messages and information in the console.&#xA;In this article, we will look at these differences in detail and understand when to use each function effectively.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;The Purpose of console.log When to Use console.log Example Usage of console.log The Purpose of console.error When to Use console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between console.log and console.info</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console.log-and-console.info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-console.log-and-console.info/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to debugging and logging messages in JavaScript, two commonly used methods are console.log and console.info.&#xA;Although they may seem similar, they have distinct characteristics that make them useful in different scenarios.&#xA;In this article, we will look at the differences between console.log and console.info and learn when to use each method effectively.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Overview of console.log Understanding console.info Differences between console.log and console.info Output appearance Default behavior Message importance Log levels Use cases for console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Check If a String Contains a Substring in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/string-contains-a-substring-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/string-contains-a-substring-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Checking whether a string contains a specific substring is a common requirement in JavaScript programming.&#xA;Whether you need to validate user input or search for specific patterns within a larger string, having the ability to check for substrings is crucial.&#xA;This article will guide you through the process of checking for substrings in JavaScript, providing you with the necessary knowledge to implement this functionality in your projects.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Using the indexOf() Method Utilizing the includes() Method Employing Regular Expressions (RegExp) Comparing Performance Considerations Case Sensitivity in Substring Checks Wrap Up FAQs Using the indexOf() Method The indexOf() method is a built-in JavaScript function that allows you to find the position of a substring within a string.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove a Specific Element from an Array in JavaScript</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-specific-element-from-array-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-specific-element-from-array-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Arrays are a fundamental data structure in JavaScript, and they allow you to store multiple values in a single variable.&#xA;However, there are scenarios where you may want to remove a particular element from an array to modify its contents.&#xA;In this article, we will look at different approaches to achieve this task effectively.&#xA;We will cover various methods and techniques that allow you to remove an element from an array based on its value or index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do JavaScript Closures Work? An Easy Explanation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-do-closures-work-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-do-closures-work-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>JavaScript is a versatile programming language widely used for web development. It supports various powerful features that make it popular among developers.&#xA;One such feature is closures, which enable the creation of powerful and flexible code structures.&#xA;In this article, we will look at the concept of JavaScript closures, understand how they work, and explore their practical applications.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Understanding lexical scope What is a closure? Creating a closure in JavaScript The anatomy of a closure Practical uses of closures 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Powerful GPT?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-is-the-most-powerful-gpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-is-the-most-powerful-gpt/</guid>
      <description>Over the years, language models have undergone significant advancements, revolutionizing the field of natural language processing (NLP).&#xA;Among the notable milestones in this domain are the series of Generative Pre-trained Transformer (GPT) models developed by various organizations.&#xA;These models have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in tasks such as text generation, comprehension, and language understanding.&#xA;From the groundbreaking GPT-2 to the latest GPT-4, these models have continually pushed the boundaries of what is possible in the realm of AI-driven language processing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is DALL-E and Where Does DALL-E Get Its Data From?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-dall-e-and-where-does-dall-e-get-its-data-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-dall-e-and-where-does-dall-e-get-its-data-from/</guid>
      <description>DALL-E, also known as DALL-E 2, is an impressive large language model (LLM) developed by OpenAI.&#xA;Its primary function is to generate images based on textual descriptions.&#xA;By training on a vast dataset comprising text from various sources such as books, articles, websites, and social media, alongside images gathered from platforms like Google Images, Flickr, and Pinterest, DALL-E has become a revolutionary tool in the field of image generation.&#xA;Understanding DALL-E&amp;rsquo;s Training Dataset The training dataset used to train DALL-E is a comprehensive collection of paired text and image data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Owns ChatGPT and Who Created It? All You Need to Know</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/who-owns-chatgpt-and-who-created-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/who-owns-chatgpt-and-who-created-it/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT, a groundbreaking language model, has captured the attention of many with its ability to generate human-like text and provide informative responses.&#xA;But who are the minds behind this remarkable technology, and who holds its ownership? In this article, we will look at the details of ChatGPT&amp;rsquo;s creation and ownership.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is ChatGPT? The Birth of OpenAI The Development of ChatGPT The CEO of ChatGPT ChatGPT and Microsoft Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s Relationship with OpenAI Wrap Up FAQs What is ChatGPT?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Programming Language is ChatGPT Coded In?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/programming-language-is-chatgpt-coded-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/programming-language-is-chatgpt-coded-in/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT, one of the most advanced language models developed by OpenAI, is coded in Python.&#xA;Python is a versatile and widely-used programming language that finds extensive application in various domains, including data science, machine learning, and artificial intelligence.&#xA;Its simplicity, powerful libraries, and active community make it an ideal choice for building complex models like ChatGPT.&#xA;In this article, we will look deeper into the reasons why Python stands out as an excellent programming language for coding ChatGPT, exploring its features, versatility, and benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does ChatGPT Give the Same Answer to Everyone?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/does-chatgpt-give-the-same-answer-to-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/does-chatgpt-give-the-same-answer-to-everyone/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT is a remarkable language model that has the ability to generate text similar to that of human-written content.&#xA;However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that ChatGPT does not provide the same answer to everyone.&#xA;The responses generated by ChatGPT are influenced by several factors, ensuring a unique and tailored experience for each user.&#xA;Factors influencing ChatGPT&amp;rsquo;s responses When interacting with ChatGPT, the following elements contribute to the varied responses it produces:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Compare Strings in Java?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-compare-strings-in-java/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-compare-strings-in-java/</guid>
      <description>Strings in Java are objects that represent a sequence of characters. Comparing strings involves determining if they are equal, less than, or greater than each other based on their content.&#xA;Java provides several methods to perform string comparison efficiently and accurately.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;1. String Comparison using equals() 2. String Comparison using compareTo() 3. String Comparison using equalsIgnoreCase() 4. String Comparison using regionMatches() 5. String Comparison using Regular Expressions Performance Considerations Best Practices for String Comparison Wrap Up FAQs 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between Machine Learning and Generative AI </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-machine-learning-and-generative-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-machine-learning-and-generative-ai/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is a rapidly advancing field that encompasses various subfields, including machine learning and generative AI.&#xA;While both machine learning and generative AI are branches of AI, they differ in their objectives and methodologies.&#xA;This article aims to elaborate on the difference between machine learning and generative AI, highlighting on their respective goals, techniques, and applications.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Machine Learning: Learning from Data Supervised Learning Unsupervised Learning Reinforcement Learning Generative AI: Creating New Data Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) Variational Autoencoders (VAEs) Applications Machine Learning Applications Generative AI Applications Wrap Up Machine Learning: Learning from Data Machine learning is an AI discipline that enables computers to learn from data without explicit programming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between ChatGPT and Search Engine (Google Search)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-chatgpt-and-a-search-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-chatgpt-and-a-search-engine/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT and search engines (like Google search and Bing) are powerful tools that can be used to find information.&#xA;But, they have different capabilities and limitations, and they are used for different purposes.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;ChatGPT: A Conversational Language Model Function and Capabilities Limitations Applications Search Engine: A Gateway to Information Function and Capabilities Weaknesses/Downside Applications Wrap Up FAQs ChatGPT: A Conversational Language Model ChatGPT is a large language model that is trained on a massive dataset of text and code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can ChatGPT Replace Search Engines like Google?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/can-chatgpt-replace-search-engines-like-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/can-chatgpt-replace-search-engines-like-google/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT is a large language model (LLM) chatbot developed by OpenAI. It is trained on a massive dataset of text and code, and it can generate human-like text, translate languages, write different kinds of creative content, and answer your questions in an informative way.&#xA;Read on: Where Does ChatGPT Get Its Data From?&#xA;However, ChatGPT is not a search engine. Search engines like Google index billions of web pages and use algorithms to rank them based on relevance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Are the Limitations of ChatGPT?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-are-the-limitations-of-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-are-the-limitations-of-chatgpt/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT is an advanced language model that has gained significant attention and popularity due to its ability to generate human-like responses.&#xA;But, it is essential to understand that, like any tool, ChatGPT has its limitations. In this article, we will look at and elaborate on the limitations of ChatGPT, highlighting on areas where it may fall short in providing accurate, complete, and interpretable responses.&#xA;By understanding these limitations, users can make informed decisions about the appropriate use and potential challenges they may encounter when utilizing ChatGPT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of ChatGPT on Students: Positive and Negative Effect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/impact-of-chatgpt-on-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/impact-of-chatgpt-on-students/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT, an advanced language model developed by OpenAI, has gained substantial attention for its potential impact on various aspects of human life.&#xA;In the context of education, ChatGPT can have both positive and negative effects on students.&#xA;In this article, we will look at the implications of ChatGPT on students&amp;rsquo; communication, learning, creativity, as well as address potential concerns such as distraction, misinformation, and cheating.&#xA;In addition, we will provide useful tips for students to maximize the benefits of using ChatGPT while avoiding its potential pitfalls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is ChatGPT? Its Advantages and Disadvantages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-chatgpt-and-its-advantages-and-disadvantages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-chatgpt-and-its-advantages-and-disadvantages/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is ChatGPT? Advantages of ChatGPT 1. Extensive Training and Reliable Responses 2. Versatility and Multifaceted Capabilities 3. Ease of Use and Accessibility Limitations and Disadvantages 1. Potential for Bias in Responses 2. Possibility of Inaccurate or Misleading Text 3. Potential for Misuse and Ethical Concerns Wrap Up FAQs (Frequently Asked Questions) What is ChatGPT? ChatGPT is an advanced language model chatbot created by OpenAI. It boasts several advantages that make it a valuable tool for various applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Long Does It Take to Learn Basic Computer Skills?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-long-does-it-take-to-learn-basic-computer-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-long-does-it-take-to-learn-basic-computer-skills/</guid>
      <description>Basic computer skills have become essential for individuals from all walks of life in the present digital age.&#xA;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a student, a professional, or a retiree, having a solid understanding of computers and technology can greatly enhance your personal and professional life.&#xA;But a common question that arises is, “How long does it take to learn basic computer skills?”&#xA;In this guide, we will look at the various aspects of learning basic computer skills, including the time it takes, the resources available, and tips for effective learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to access an array that is nested in an object? (Javascript)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-do-you-access-an-array-that-is-nested-in-an-object/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-do-you-access-an-array-that-is-nested-in-an-object/</guid>
      <description>To access an array that is nested in an object, you need to navigate through the object&amp;rsquo;s properties and indexes.&#xA;There are basically two methods that you can use to access an array that is nested in an object. Let&amp;rsquo;s look into the methods.&#xA;Method 1: Dot notation One way to access a nested array in an object is by using the dot notation. This method allows you to access properties and sub-properties of an object.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 5 Best JSON File Viewer for Macs: View, Edit and Debug</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-best-json-file-viewer-for-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-best-json-file-viewer-for-mac/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a Mac user and frequently work with JSON files, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a reliable JSON file viewer to help you navigate, edit, and format JSON data.&#xA;Fortunately, there are many great options available for Mac users. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll provide a detailed overview of five of the most popular JSON file viewers for Mac, along with links to download the apps.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;1. Visual Studio Code (VS Code) 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best CSV Editors for Macs: View, Edit, and Format</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/the-best-csv-editors-or-tools-for-macs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/the-best-csv-editors-or-tools-for-macs/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to working with CSV (Comma Separated Values) files on your Mac, having the right editor can make a significant difference in your productivity and overall experience.&#xA;In this article, we will look at some of the best CSV editors available for Macs. Each editor offers unique features and functionalities, allowing you to view, edit, and format CSV files efficiently.&#xA;Whether you need a powerful IDE, a fast and flexible text editor, or a free and open-source option, we have got you covered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming Forums for Beginners</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/programming-forums-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/programming-forums-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>If you are a beginner in programming and looking for a supportive community to enhance your skills, programming forums are the perfect place for you.&#xA;In these forums, you can interact with experienced programmers, ask questions, seek guidance, and find resources to help you learn programming.&#xA;In this article, we will look at some of the best programming forums that cater specifically to beginners.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;1. Stack Overflow 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Laptop Screen Size Is Best for Programming?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-screen-size-is-best-for-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-screen-size-is-best-for-programming/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to programming, choosing the right screen size is crucial for a comfortable and productive coding experience.&#xA;The screen size you opt for can significantly impact your ability to view and manipulate code efficiently.&#xA;In this article, we will look into various factors to consider when selecting a screen size for programming and provide recommendations based on industry standards and user preferences.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Factors to Consider for Choosing the Best Screen Size 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much GB is required for a programming laptop?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-much-gb-is-required-for-a-programming-laptop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-much-gb-is-required-for-a-programming-laptop/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to choosing a programming laptop, one of the crucial considerations is the amount of storage space it offers.&#xA;The storage capacity you need depends on various factors, including the type of programming you do, the size of your projects, and your personal preferences.&#xA;In this article, we will look into the recommended storage space for programming laptops and provide insights to help you make an informed decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much RAM is Needed for Coding in a Laptop?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-much-ram-is-needed-for-coding-in-laptop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-much-ram-is-needed-for-coding-in-laptop/</guid>
      <description>If you are a programmer, you might be wondering how much RAM is needed for coding in a laptop.&#xA;The amount of RAM you need can vary depending on several factors, such as the type of programming you do, the size of your projects, and your personal preferences.&#xA;In this article, we will look at these factors in detail and provide recommendations for the amount of RAM you should consider for coding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Processor is Best for Coding or Programming?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-processor-is-best-for-coding-or-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-processor-is-best-for-coding-or-programming/</guid>
      <description>Are you a coder or programmer looking to upgrade your computer&amp;rsquo;s processor or get a new computer with a better processor?&#xA;Choosing the right processor is crucial for optimal performance and productivity in coding and programming tasks.&#xA;In this article, we will discuss some of the best processors for coding and programming, considering factors such as power, affordability, and performance.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and find the perfect processor for your needs!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i3 or i5: Which is Better for College Students?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-i3-or-i5-better-for-college-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-i3-or-i5-better-for-college-students/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to choosing a laptop for college, one of the most important considerations is the processor.&#xA;The processor plays a significant role in determining the performance and capabilities of your laptop.&#xA;Two popular options in the market are the Intel i3 and i5 processors. In this article, we will look at the differences between the i3 and i5 processors and help you determine which one is better for college students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Current Port Number in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-get-current-port-number-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-get-current-port-number-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Before we look at how to get the current port number in JavaScript, we need to understand what port numbers are?&#xA;Understanding port numbers in URLs Suppose we have the URL: http://example.com:8080/path/to/page&#xA;In this example, the port number is 8080. It is appended to the domain name example.com and separated by a colon (:).&#xA;This specific port allows the web server to listen for incoming requests on that port.&#xA;Please note that the actual port number used in URLs can vary depending on the specific web application or service being accessed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Programming Language is Used for Hacking?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-programming-language-is-used-for-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/which-programming-language-is-used-for-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered which programming languages are used by hackers to carry out their malicious activities?&#xA;In this article, we will look into the world of hacking and dive into the programming languages that play a crucial role in these activities.&#xA;But before we dive in, let&amp;rsquo;s first understand what hacking is, who hackers are, and the importance of programming in the hacking realm.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is Hacking?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Hackers Better Than Programmers?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/are-hackers-better-than-programmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/are-hackers-better-than-programmers/</guid>
      <description>Are hackers better than programmers? This question often sparks a lively debate among tech enthusiasts and professionals.&#xA;Both hackers and programmers possess valuable skills that contribute to the ever-evolving world of technology.&#xA;In this article, we will look at the attributes and expertise of hackers and programmers, highlighting on their respective strengths and roles within the field.&#xA;So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and uncover the truth behind the question: Are hackers better than programmers?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT a Strong or Weak AI?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-chatgpt-a-strong-or-weak-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-chatgpt-a-strong-or-weak-ai/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is a hot topic in today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly advancing technological landscape.&#xA;ChatGPT is one of the most popular forms of AI, and in this article, we will explore its nature and determine whether it can be classified as a strong or weak AI.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Overview of ChatGPT: A Weak AI What is Strong AI? The Power of ChatGPT as a Tool Wrap Up FAQs Overview of ChatGPT: A Weak AI ChatGPT is an extraordinary creation of artificial intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is != and !== in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-not-equal-and-strict-not-equal-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-not-equal-and-strict-not-equal-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>JavaScript provides two comparison operators, != and !==, which are used to compare two values and determine their equality.&#xA;These operators play a crucial role in JavaScript programming, as they allow developers to perform comparisons and make decisions based on the results.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;The != Operator The !== Operator Usage of != and !== Operators Wrap Up Frequently Asked Questions The != Operator The != operator is known as the “not equal” operator in JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between || and &amp;&amp; in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-logical-or-and-logical-and-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-logical-or-and-logical-and-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>In JavaScript, the || (logical OR) and &amp;amp;&amp;amp; (logical AND) operators are used to combine two or more expressions and return a Boolean value.&#xA;The &amp;amp;&amp;amp; operator returns true if both of its operands are true, and false otherwise. The || operator returns true if either of its operands are true, and false otherwise.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;|| (Logical OR) Operator || (Logical OR) Operation || (Logical OR) Example Code Usage with Non-Boolean Values Usage in Conditional Statements Usage in Loops &amp;amp;&amp;amp; (Logical AND) Operator &amp;amp;&amp;amp; (Logical AND) Operation &amp;amp;&amp;amp; (Logical AND) Example Code Usage with Non-Boolean Values Usage in Conditional Statements Usage in Loops Usage in Functions Wrap Up FAQs || (Logical OR) Operator The || operator in JavaScript is primarily used to combine expressions and return the value of the first truthy operand encountered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Shuffle an Array Randomly in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-shuffle-an-array-randomly-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-shuffle-an-array-randomly-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>In JavaScript, shuffling an array randomly can be a useful technique when you want to randomize the order of elements.&#xA;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re building a game, conducting statistical analysis, or simply adding some randomness to your application, understanding how to shuffle an array is essential.&#xA;In this article, we will provide a detailed explanation of the code used to shuffle an array randomly in JavaScript. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;The Code Understanding the Code Step 1: Initializing the Array Step 2: Looping through the Array Step 3: Generating a Random Index Step 4: Swapping Elements Step 5: Repeat Until Shuffled Step 6: Console Log the Shuffled Array The Code const array = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]; for (let i = array.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Download Images from URL in Node.js?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-download-image-from-url-in-node-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-download-image-from-url-in-node-js/</guid>
      <description>When working with Node.js, you may come across situations where you need to download images from a given URL.&#xA;This article will guide you through the process of downloading images from a URL in Node.js, providing step-by-step instructions and code snippets to help you accomplish this task effectively.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;How to Download Image from URL in Node.js 1. Installing Dependencies 2. Writing the Download Function 3. Implementing the Image Download How to Download Image from URL in Node.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Download Multiple Images in Node.js</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-download-multiple-images-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-download-multiple-images-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>Downloading multiple images in Node.js can be efficiently accomplished using the Promise and async/await features.&#xA;In this article, we are going to look at how to achieve this in your Node.js projects.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Installation and Setup Downloading Multiple Images Handling Errors Validating Image URLs Installation and Setup To begin, ensure that you have Node.js installed on your system. Then, follow these steps to set up your project:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Check if an Image URL is Valid in JavaScript?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-check-if-an-image-url-is-valid-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-check-if-an-image-url-is-valid-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>When working with image URLs in JavaScript, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to ensure their validity. This article provides a comprehensive guide on how to check if an image URL is valid in JavaScript, along with code examples.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Understanding Image URL Validation Ways to Check if an Image URL is Valid in JavaScript? 1. Using Regular Expressions 2. Using the Fetch API 3. Utilizing External Libraries FAQs Understanding Image URL Validation Validating an image URL ensures that the URL points to an existing and accessible image file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the Difference Between # and ## in Python?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-single-hash-and-double-hash-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-single-hash-and-double-hash-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Python, as a versatile programming language, offers various features to make coding more efficient and readable.&#xA;One such feature is the ability to include comments in the code. Comments are lines of text that are not executed by the interpreter and are solely meant to provide additional information or context about the code.&#xA;They serve as helpful notes to make the code more understandable to other developers or even to the future self.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the Difference Between Using [] and {} in Python?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-using-square-bracket-and-curly-braces-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-difference-between-using-square-bracket-and-curly-braces-in-python/</guid>
      <description>The square brackets [] in Python are used to denote a list, while the curly braces {} are used to denote a dictionary.&#xA;These symbols play a significant role in Python&amp;rsquo;s data structures, and understanding their differences is essential for efficient programming.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What Are Lists in Python? Creating Lists in Python Accessing Elements in a List Modifying Lists What Are Dictionaries in Python? Creating Dictionaries in Python Accessing Values in a Dictionary Modifying Dictionaries Wrap Up FAQs What Are Lists in Python?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between / and // in Python with Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-/-and-/-in-python-with-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-/-and-/-in-python-with-example/</guid>
      <description>If you are new to Python, you might have come across the symbols “/“ and “//“ in mathematical operations, particularly in division.&#xA;The forward slash “/“ serves as a normal division, while the double forward slash “//“ serves as a floor division.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;The “/“ Operator: Normal Division Example: The “//“ Operator: Floor Division Example: Wrap Up The “/“ Operator: Normal Division The forward slash “/“ is the standard division operator in Python.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Clear the Terminal in VS Code?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-clear-terminal-in-vs-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-clear-terminal-in-vs-code/</guid>
      <description>The terminal in Visual Studio Code (VS Code) is a powerful tool that allows developers to run commands, execute scripts, and debug code efficiently.&#xA;However, over time, the terminal can accumulate output from previous commands, causing clutter and hindering productivity.&#xA;To optimize your coding experience, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to know how to clear the terminal effectively.&#xA;In this article, we will look at multiple ways to clear the terminal in VS Code, ensuring a fresh and organized workspace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Numbers from a String in Python using Regex?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-numbers-from-a-string-in-python-using-regex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-numbers-from-a-string-in-python-using-regex/</guid>
      <description>When working with strings in Python, you might encounter situations where you need to remove specific characters, such as numbers.&#xA;Using regex can provide an effective way to achieve this, as it allows you to define complex patterns for matching and replacing text within strings.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Importing the re Module Creating the Regex Pattern Using re.sub() to Remove Numbers Example Code for Removing Numbers from a String: Wrap Up FAQs Importing the re Module The first step is to import the re module, which stands for “regular expressions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix &#34;Module not found: Can&#39;t resolve encoding&#34; in Next.js</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/module-not-found-cant-resolve-encoding-in-next-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/module-not-found-cant-resolve-encoding-in-next-js/</guid>
      <description>The error “Module not found: Can&amp;rsquo;t resolve encoding” in Next.js typically arises when the encoding module is missing from your project&amp;rsquo;s dependencies.&#xA;This module plays a crucial role in handling the encoding and decoding of strings, which is essential for various functionalities within Next.js, including the popular useRouter hook.&#xA;How to Fix the Error Resolving this error involves a few straightforward steps. Follow these instructions to get your project back on track:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Check if a Variable is a Number in Python?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-check-if-a-variable-is-a-number-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-check-if-a-variable-is-a-number-in-python/</guid>
      <description>In Python, variables can hold various types of data, including integers (int) and floating-point numbers (float).&#xA;When dealing with dynamic data, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to ascertain whether a variable contains a numeric value before performing mathematical operations.&#xA;We will discuss two methods that help you achieve this goal: the type() function and the isinstance() function.&#xA;1. Making Use of the type() Function — Defining the Function def is_number(variable): &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; This function checks if a variable is a number.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Import Instead of Require in Node.js?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-use-import-instead-of-require-in-node-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-use-import-instead-of-require-in-node-js/</guid>
      <description>Node.js has been using the &#39;require()&#39; syntax for module loading for a long time.&#xA;However, the introduction of ECMAScript (ES) modules has brought a more streamlined and standardized way of importing modules using the &amp;lsquo;import&amp;rsquo; syntax.&#xA;Steps on How to Use Import Instead of Require in Node.js To transition from &#39;require()&#39; to &#39;import&#39;, follow these steps:&#xA;Step 1: Update Your package.json The first step is to open your project&amp;rsquo;s package.json file and add the “type” field with the value “module”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Node.js Used for Backend or Frontend?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-nodejs-used-for-backend-or-frontend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/is-nodejs-used-for-backend-or-frontend/</guid>
      <description>Node.js is a JavaScript runtime environment that can be used to create both client-side and server-side applications.&#xA;So, is Node.js used for backend or frontend development?&#xA;The answer is both. Node.js is a versatile platform that can be used for a variety of development tasks.&#xA;It is a popular choice for both backend and frontend development because of its event-driven, non-blocking architecture, scalability, and performance.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Frontend Development with Node.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix &#34;Your Devices Were Logged Out&#34; Error on WhatsApp?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-your-devices-were-logged-out-error-on-whatsapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-your-devices-were-logged-out-error-on-whatsapp/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve encountered the error message “Your devices were logged out due to an unexpected issue, please relink your device” on WhatsApp, don&amp;rsquo;t worry; you&amp;rsquo;re not alone.&#xA;This error indicates that your linked devices have been logged out due to a problem with syncing data from your phone.&#xA;In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to fix this issue and ensure that your WhatsApp experience remains smooth and secure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Stop or Disable VSCode Auto Update?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-stop-or-disable-vscode-auto-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-stop-or-disable-vscode-auto-update/</guid>
      <description>Visual Studio Code (VS Code) is a powerful and widely used code editor, loved by developers for its versatility and features.&#xA;However, one aspect that might not sit well with everyone is its default auto-update feature.&#xA;While staying up-to-date is essential for security and performance reasons, some users prefer to have more control over when and how their software updates.&#xA;In this article, we will guide you through the steps to stop or disable the auto-update feature in VS Code, ensuring you can manage updates on your terms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Mute or Unmute Group Notifications on WhatsApp?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-mute-or-unmute-group-notifications-on-whatsapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-mute-or-unmute-group-notifications-on-whatsapp/</guid>
      <description>WhatsApp is one of the most popular messaging apps in the world, connecting people across the globe.&#xA;However, being part of multiple group chats can sometimes lead to a flood of notifications, making it challenging to maintain your peace and focus.&#xA;Fortunately, WhatsApp offers a solution by allowing you to mute group notifications or unmute them when you&amp;rsquo;re ready to rejoin the conversation.&#xA;In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to effectively manage group notifications on WhatsApp, ensuring a more peaceful and organized messaging experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix Git Error &#34;Unable to Resolve Reference refs/remotes/origin/master Reference Broken&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-git-error-unable-to-resolve-reference-refs-remotes-origin-master-reference-broken/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-git-error-unable-to-resolve-reference-refs-remotes-origin-master-reference-broken/</guid>
      <description>The Git error message “Unable to resolve reference refs/remotes/origin/master reference broken” often occur when running a git pull command.&#xA;This error indicates that Git is unable to lock the reference for the master branch in the remote repository.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s a frustrating issue, but fear not; we&amp;rsquo;ll guide you through the steps to resolve it.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Reasons Why this Error Occur? Steps to Resolve the Error 1. Check if the remote repository is available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Text Wrap to Next Line in CSS?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-make-text-wrap-to-next-line-in-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-make-text-wrap-to-next-line-in-css/</guid>
      <description>If a line of text in HTML is not breaking, and it is leading to the overflow of the text, here are some ways you can fix it.&#xA;Step on How to Fix Text Not Wrapping in CSS 1. By Using the Word-Wrap Property To address the issue of text overflow in CSS, the word-wrap property comes in handy.&#xA;This property allows long words to be broken and wrap onto the next line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to open Visual Studio Code&#39;s &#39;settings.json&#39; file?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-open-settings.json-in-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-open-settings.json-in-vscode/</guid>
      <description>Visual Studio Code (VS Code) is a powerful and versatile code editor used by developers worldwide.&#xA;One of the key features that make it so flexible is the ability to customize settings to suit your coding preferences.&#xA;In this article, we will look at two methods that you can use to open the settings.json file in VS Code, allowing you to customize your IDE.&#xA;1. By Using the Command Palette a).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Find and Replace in VSCode?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-use-find-and-replace-in-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-use-find-and-replace-in-vscode/</guid>
      <description>One of the powerful features that can save you time and effort while working with text or code in VSCode is the “Find and Replace” feature.&#xA;In this article, we will look at how to use the Find and Replace feature in VSCode.&#xA;Steps on How to Use Find and Replace in VSCode Open Your File: Begin by opening the file where you want to find and replace text.&#xA;Shortcut for Find/Replace Dialog Box: Press Ctrl+F (Windows/Linux).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Find Your GitHub Username?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-find-your-github-username/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-find-your-github-username/</guid>
      <description>GitHub is a web-based platform designed for developers and programmers to collaborate on projects, track changes in code, and manage version control.&#xA;It plays a crucial role in the world of software development, making it easier for teams to work together, share code, and contribute to open-source projects.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;How Does GitHub Usernames Look Like? Ways on How to Find Your GitHub Username 1. Using the GitHub Website 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Clear npm Cache?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-clear-npm-cache/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-clear-npm-cache/</guid>
      <description>The npm cache is essentially a local storage area where npm retains downloaded packages and their dependencies.&#xA;Its primary goal is to aid package installations by reducing the need for constant internet downloads.&#xA;However, over time, the npm cache can become a source of issues.&#xA;In this guide, we will look at why clearing the npm cache is necessary and how to clear it.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Why Clear the npm Cache?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix npm Installation Error: npm ERR! code EINTEGRITY?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-npm-installation-error-npm-err-code-eintegrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-npm-installation-error-npm-err-code-eintegrity/</guid>
      <description>When working on a frontend application, encountering the npm ERR! code EINTEGRITY error can be frustrating.&#xA;This error occurs during or after an npm install command and indicates that there is a mismatch between the expected and actual integrity checksum of a package during installation.&#xA;In this article, we will look at the causes of this error and how you can resolve it.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Common Causes of EINTEGRITY Errors Steps on How to Fix &amp;ldquo;npm ERR!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Delete Node Modules in VSCode?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-delete-node-modules-in-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-delete-node-modules-in-vscode/</guid>
      <description>Frontend application projects often come with a hefty luggage known as the node_modules folder.&#xA;While these modules are essential for the project&amp;rsquo;s functionality, they can sometimes become a burden, taking up significant disk space or even become corrupted as it may contain outdated or conflicting data.&#xA;In this guide, we will look at two methods on how to delete the node modules in Visual Studio Code (VSCode).&#xA;Methods on How to Delete Node Modules Folder in VSCode 1: Using the Right-Click Menu You can delete the node modules in VSCode by right-clicking on the node module folder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix &#34;Remove-Item: A parameter cannot be found that matches parameter name &#39;rf&#39;&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/remove-item-a-parameter-cannot-be-found-that-matches-parameter-name-rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/remove-item-a-parameter-cannot-be-found-that-matches-parameter-name-rf/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a Window/PowerShell user, you may have encountered the following error message:&#xA;Remove-Item : A parameter cannot be found that matches parameter name &amp;#39;rf&amp;#39;. At line:1 char:4 + rm -rf node_modules + ~~~ + CategoryInfo : InvalidArgument: (:) [Remove-Item], ParameterBindingException + FullyQualifiedErrorId : NamedParameterNotFound,Microsoft.PowerShell.Commands.RemoveItem Command &amp;#x1f4a1;&#xA;I encounter this error when trying to remove node_modules folder from a &amp;ldquo;next.js&amp;rdquo; project using VSCode&amp;rsquo;s terminal.&#xA;This error occurs when you try to use the rm (or Remove-Item) command with the -rf flags to recursively force remove a directory or file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to setup C/C&#43;&#43; in Visual Studio Code?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-setup-c-and-cpp-in-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-setup-c-and-cpp-in-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <description>Are you trying to learn C or C++ programming using Visual Studio Code, or are you experiencing issues during the installation process?&#xA;In this guide, we will walk you through the step-by-step process of installing the &amp;ldquo;MinGW&amp;rdquo; compiler and running C and C++ programs in Visual Studio Code.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Steps on how to set up C/C++ in Visual Studio Code: 1/ Download MinGW 2/ Install MinGW 3/ Configure MinGW Installation 4/ Complete the Installation 5/ Configure Environment Variables 6/ Verify MinGW Installation 7/ Create a C/C++ File in Visual Studio Code 8/ Install the Code Runner Extension Troubleshooting &amp;#x26a0;&amp;#xfe0f; Here is an Installation Video for More Guide: Steps on how to set up C/C++ in Visual Studio Code: 1/ Download MinGW The first step in setting up your C/C++ development environment is to download the MinGW (Minimalist GNU for Windows) compiler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C vs C&#43;&#43; vs C#: What&#39;s the Difference?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/c-vs-cpp-vs-csharp-whats-the-difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/c-vs-cpp-vs-csharp-whats-the-difference/</guid>
      <description>Programming languages are the building blocks of the digital world, and among the most prominent trio of languages is C, C++, and C#.&#xA;These three languages, while sharing some similarities, serve distinct purposes in the world of software development.&#xA;In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll look into the history, features, code syntax, applications, and provide a comparative table to help you understand the differences and make an informed choice for your programming journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C Program to Calculate the Average of N Numbers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/c-program-to-calculate-the-average-of-n-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/c-program-to-calculate-the-average-of-n-numbers/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we are going to look at a C program that can be used to calculate the average of “N” numbers.&#xA;We will be using an array to store the numbers.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;The C Program to Calculate the Average of N Numbers: Explanation of the code step by step: Wrap Up The C Program to Calculate the Average of N Numbers: #include &amp;lt;stdio.h&amp;gt; int main() { int n; printf(&amp;#34;Enter number of elements: &amp;#34;); scanf(&amp;#34;%d&amp;#34;, &amp;amp;n); int avgArr[n]; printf(&amp;#34;Enter each number:\n&amp;#34;); for (int i = 0; i &amp;lt; n; i++) { scanf(&amp;#34;%d&amp;#34;, &amp;amp;avgArr[i]); } int sum = 0; for (int i = 0; i &amp;lt; n; i++) { sum += avgArr[i]; } double result = (double)sum / n; printf(&amp;#34;Resultant is: %.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between System Software and Application Software with Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-system-software-and-application-software-with-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/difference-between-system-software-and-application-software-with-examples/</guid>
      <description>Computer software is a set of instructions that tells a computer what to do. It is made up of two main types: system software and application software.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What is System Software? Examples of System Software Features of System Software What is Application Software? Examples of Application Software Features of Application Software The Key Differences Between System and Application Software Wrap Up FAQs 1. Can a computer function without system software?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open VS Code Terminal in Another Window?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-open-vscode-terminal-in-another-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-open-vscode-terminal-in-another-window/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of the default VS Code terminal that&amp;rsquo;s tucked away at the bottom of your screen? Do you want to open it in a new window, giving you more workspace and flexibility for your coding projects?&#xA;In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll look at the steps you can follow to open the VS Code terminal in a separate window, making your coding experience more efficient and enjoyable.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Steps on How to Open VSCode Terminal in a Separate Window Step 1: Open the File Step 2: Create a New Window Step 3: Launch the Terminal Step 4: Navigate to Your Workspace FAQs Steps on How to Open VSCode Terminal in a Separate Window Step 1: Open the File First, open the file you want to work on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Delete VSCode Cached Data Files?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-delete-vscode-cached-data-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-delete-vscode-cached-data-files/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to working on files in Visual Studio Code (VSCode), you may have noticed that over time, the software&amp;rsquo;s performance starts to slow down.&#xA;One common reason for this is the accumulation of cached files. Though cached data can be helpful for quick access to files, but it can also slow down your system.&#xA;In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll look at how to delete or remove VSCode cached data files to ensure that your coding experience is smooth and efficient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Circular Image in CSS?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-make-a-circular-image-in-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-make-a-circular-image-in-css/</guid>
      <description>In web development, styling images is a common practice to enhance the visual appeal of a website.&#xA;One popular design choice is to make images circular, providing a sleek and modern look.&#xA;Achieving this effect in CSS is straightforward, primarily utilizing the border-radius property.&#xA;In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the steps to create a circular image and provide a simple example for you to try.&#xA;How to Make an Image Rounded in CSS?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fix error hydration failed because the initial UI does not match what was rendered on the server in nextJS?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-error-hydration-failed-because-the-initial-ui-does-not-match-what-was-rendered-on-the-server-in-nextjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-error-hydration-failed-because-the-initial-ui-does-not-match-what-was-rendered-on-the-server-in-nextjs/</guid>
      <description>The error “Hydration failed because the initial UI does not match what was rendered on the server” occurs in Next.js when there is a difference between the HTML markup generated on the server and the HTML markup rendered on the client-side.&#xA;This mismatch disrupts the hydration process, which is responsible for attaching event listeners and making the page interactive.&#xA;&amp;#x1f4a1;&#xA;In Next.js, hydration is the process of transforming the server-rendered HTML into a fully interactive React application, enabling user interactions and a seamless user experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the purpose of semicolons (;) in C language?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-purpose-of-semicolons-in-c-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-is-the-purpose-of-semicolons-in-c-language/</guid>
      <description>When writing a C program, a semicolon (;) is used after each line of code. This might seem tedious, but it is essential for ensuring the correct interpretation and execution of the code.&#xA;Why is semicolon (;) needed in C language? Some of the reasons why semicolon is used in C programming is discussed below.&#xA;1. For statement termination In C, statements are the fundamental building blocks of code, representing instructions or actions that the program should execute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Semicolons Needed in CSS?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/are-semicolons-needed-in-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/are-semicolons-needed-in-css/</guid>
      <description>Yes, in CSS, semicolons are needed to separate each statement to avoid code misinterpretation or potential errors.&#xA;Note that if there&amp;rsquo;s only one CSS statement declaration, no ending semicolon is required.&#xA;For example:&#xA;p { font-size: 30px } However, if there are multiple statement declarations, you need to separate them with semicolons:&#xA;p { font-size: 30px; text-align: center; } While it&amp;rsquo;s technically optional to use a semicolon at the end of the last statement when there are multiple declarations, it&amp;rsquo;s highly recommended to include it for consistency and to prevent potential errors if you add more statements later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make a placeholder for a &#39;select&#39; box?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-make-a-placeholder-for-a-select-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-make-a-placeholder-for-a-select-box/</guid>
      <description>Select boxes, while versatile, lack a built-in placeholder attribute similar to input fields.&#xA;However, there are several effective methods to create a placeholder effect that enhances user experience.&#xA;How to make a placeholder for a &amp;lsquo;select&amp;rsquo; box? To create a placeholder for a &amp;lt;select&amp;gt; box, you can use the following methods:&#xA;Method 1/ Disabled and Selected Option In this method, the first &amp;lt;option&amp;gt; is disabled, preventing users from selecting it, and the selected attribute ensures that it is the default option displayed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Turn Off or Disable Text Selection Highlight in CSS?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-turn-off-or-disable-text-selection-highlight-in-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-turn-off-or-disable-text-selection-highlight-in-css/</guid>
      <description>CSS provides a powerful way to control the visual aspects of a webpage, and one common requirement is the ability to turn off or disable text selection highlighting.&#xA;Whether you want to enhance the design or prevent users from copying content, CSS offers a solution. In this article, we will look at how to achieve this.&#xA;How to Turn Off or Disable Text Selection Highlight in CSS? To disable text selection in CSS, use the user-select property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Items from a List While Iterating in Python?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-items-from-a-list-while-iterating-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-items-from-a-list-while-iterating-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Python, with its flexibility and power, provides various methods to manipulate lists.&#xA;However, removing items from a list while iterating can be a tricky task. In this article, we will look at several methods that will allow you to remove elements from a list while iterating through it.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;How to Remove Items from a List While Iterating in Python? 1. Creating a New List with List Comprehension: 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix PDFDrive not Working or Downloading?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-pdfdrive-not-working-or-downloading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-pdfdrive-not-working-or-downloading/</guid>
      <description>PDF Drive boasts a massive collection of free PDFs, but users often encounter frustrating download problems.&#xA;Download buttons redirecting, pages failing to load, and unresponsive buttons are common complaints.&#xA;In this article, we will look at how to fix these issues.&#xA;&amp;#x1f4a1; Quick Fix:&#xA;If the download button on PDF Drive isn&amp;rsquo;t responding, here are some quick fixes you can try.&#xA;Copy the PDF file name and try searching for the book&amp;rsquo;s title on PDFDrive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Wide is the Default `&lt;body&gt;` Margin [HTML Webpage]?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-wide-is-the-default-body-margin-webpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-wide-is-the-default-body-margin-webpage/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered about the space between the content of a web page and the edges of your browser window?&#xA;That space is often defined by the default margin of the &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; element.&#xA;In this article, we will look into the specifics of this default margin, why it matters, and how you can customize it to enhance the visual appeal of your web pages.&#xA;Default Margin in Major Browsers When you create a web page, most major browsers automatically apply a default margin of 8 pixels on all sides of the &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; element.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix Can&#39;t Download Facebook App on Android?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-cant-download-facebook-app-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-cant-download-facebook-app-on-android/</guid>
      <description>Facebook, a social media giant with a massive user community, is an integral part of our digital lives. Yet, there are instances where users encounter obstacles during the installation of the Facebook app on their Android devices.&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re facing similar problems and wondering how to fix the “Facebook is not installing on my Android” issue, this article will provide you with solutions to help you overcome this frustrating situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix WhatsApp &#34;Unable to Connect. Please try again&#34; Error?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-whatsapp-unable-to-connect-please-try-again-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-whatsapp-unable-to-connect-please-try-again-error/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there – eagerly waiting to send an important message or check the latest status updates on WhatsApp, only to be met with the frustrating “Unable to Connect. Please try again later” error.&#xA;This error message typically indicates a connectivity issue or a problem with the app&amp;rsquo;s ability to establish a connection to WhatsApp&amp;rsquo;s servers. This error can occur for several reasons.&#xA;In this article, we will look at various steps to troubleshoot and resolve this issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix Play Store Not Working &#34;Try Again&#34; Error?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-play-store-not-working-try-again-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-play-store-not-working-try-again-error/</guid>
      <description>Google Play Store, the official app store for Android devices, is a built-in part of the Android ecosystem.&#xA;However, users may encounter the frustrating “Try Again” error while attempting to search for or download an application.&#xA;In this article, we will look at practical solutions to troubleshoot and resolve this issue.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;How to Fix Play Store Not Working, “Try Again” Error? &amp;#x1f4a1; Quick Fixes: Troubleshooting Steps: 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Node.js in Windows?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-install-nodejs-in-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-install-nodejs-in-windows/</guid>
      <description>Are you working on a JavaScript project that involves server-side scripting? If so, Node.js is what you need.&#xA;Node.js has become a vital tool for developers, allowing server-side scripting and the creation of dynamic web pages.&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re a Windows user and need guidance on installing Node.js on your machine, this guide will help you through the installation process.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Steps on How to Install Node.js on Windows Step 1/ Check if you have Node.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of VSCode Useful Keyboard Shortcut Keys (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/list-of-vscode-useful-keyboard-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/list-of-vscode-useful-keyboard-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>Navigating through Visual Studio Code efficiently can significantly boost your productivity.&#xA;Mastering keyboard shortcuts is the key to unlocking the full potential of this powerful code editor.&#xA;In this article, we will explore a comprehensive list of essential and also useful VSCode keyboard shortcuts for various tasks, categorized for easy reference.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;VSCode Useful Keyboard Shortcut Keys General Commands Basic Editing Advanced Editing Region Folding Comments and Formatting Search and Replace Multi-cursor and Selection Editor Management File Management Wrap Up FAQs VSCode Useful Keyboard Shortcut Keys General Commands Ctrl+Shift+P, F1 — Show Command Palette The command palette is your go-to tool for executing any command in VSCode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix &#34;Error Couldn&#39;t Find a package.json File&#34;?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-error-couldnt-find-a-package-json-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-error-couldnt-find-a-package-json-file/</guid>
      <description>Are you facing the error “Couldn&amp;rsquo;t Find a package.json File” while trying to run a project using npm or yarn?&#xA;Don&amp;rsquo;t worry; you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. This issue can be frustrating, but fortunately, there are several ways to resolve it.&#xA;In this article, we will look at some effective solutions to help you get past this obstacle and continue with your development work smoothly.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;1. Check the Working Directory 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix VSCode Window Not Responding?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-vscode-window-not-responding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-vscode-window-not-responding/</guid>
      <description>Are you experiencing some annoying issues like VSCode window not responding, a black screen, or sluggish performance?&#xA;These problems can be incredibly frustrating, especially when you&amp;rsquo;re in the midst of a project or trying to start a new one.&#xA;Often, these issues are caused by cached VSCode files, but fear not – we have the solution.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Steps to Fix VSCode Window Not Responding Step 1: Force Close VSCode Step 2: Go to Your C:\ Drive and User’s Folder Step 3: Locate the Folder with Your Username Step 4: Access the AppData Folder Step 5: Find the Roaming Folder Step 6: Identify the “Code” Folder or Directory Step 7: Delete All Files in Cache and CachedData Step 8: Launch VSCode Again Wrap Up FAQs 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Powers Neuralink Chip When Implanted into the Human Brain?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-powers-neuralink-chip-when-implanted-into-the-human-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/what-powers-neuralink-chip-when-implanted-into-the-human-brain/</guid>
      <description>Image Credit: Neuralink&#xA;In recent years, the field of neuroscience has witnessed remarkable advancements, with one of the most talked-about innovations being the Neuralink chip.&#xA;This tiny device, developed by Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s Neuralink Corporation, holds immense potential in revolutionizing the way we interface with technology, particularly in the context of the human brain.&#xA;But have you ever wondered what powers this groundbreaking chip when it&amp;rsquo;s implanted into the human brain?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Best Lightweight Browsers for macOS (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/best-lightweight-browsers-for-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/best-lightweight-browsers-for-mac/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to browsing the internet on your Mac, having a lightweight browser can make a significant difference in performance and efficiency.&#xA;Lightweight browsers are designed to consume fewer system resources while still providing a smooth browsing experience.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s look at some of the best lightweight browsers for Mac users.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Best Lightweight Browsers for mac 1. Brave 2. Mozilla Firefox 3. DuckDuckGo 4. Opera One 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Best HTML5 Books for Beginners (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/the-best-html5-books-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/the-best-html5-books-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>HTML (HyperText Markup Language) stands as one of the fundamental languages for designing websites on the internet.&#xA;Learning HTML is an exciting journey as it provides beginners with a glimpse into the world of programming.&#xA;While many prefer video tutorials, learning from documentation or books remains one of the most effective methods.&#xA;In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll look at some of the best HTML5 books suitable for beginners.&#xA;The Best HTML5 Books for Beginners 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Delete a Git Branch Locally and Remotely?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-delete-a-git-branch-locally-and-remotely/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-delete-a-git-branch-locally-and-remotely/</guid>
      <description>Branches in a Git repo are an amazing way to add new features to a project or fix bugs while still maintaining the main codebase.&#xA;Over time, the branches you create may become too many, so you&amp;rsquo;ll want to delete some that are no longer needed.&#xA;This could be because you just created them locally, or because they&amp;rsquo;ve already been merged with the main codebase.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;How to delete a Git branch?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of Microsoft Edge Useful Keyboard Shortcuts Keys for Windows (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/list-of-microsoft-edge-useful-keyboard-shortcuts-keys-for-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/list-of-microsoft-edge-useful-keyboard-shortcuts-keys-for-windows/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Edge, the default web browser for Windows 10, offers a range of keyboard shortcuts that can enhance your browsing experience.&#xA;These shortcuts allow you to perform various tasks quickly and efficiently, saving you time and effort.&#xA;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a casual user or a power user, mastering these shortcuts can significantly improve your productivity and make browsing more convenient.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of the most useful Microsoft Edge keyboard shortcuts for Windows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cpx Module: An Alternative to the Linux cp Command for Copying Files Across Folders</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/cpx-module-an-alternative-to-the-linux-cp-command-for-copying-files-across-folders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/cpx-module-an-alternative-to-the-linux-cp-command-for-copying-files-across-folders/</guid>
      <description>I was studying a GitHub repository and decided to download a copy of the code to my machine. After running npm install, I encountered an error caused by this postinstall script:&#xA;&amp;#34;postinstall&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;cp node_modules/swiftlatex/dist/swift*.js node_modules/swiftlatex/dist/*.wasm public&amp;#34; It required the use of the cp command, which I learned is a Linux command used for copying files or folders from one part of the file system to another. It’s a powerful tool for file system operations like moving, deleting, or duplicating files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>getStaticProps and getStaticPaths Are No Longer Supported in the Next.js App Router: Use generateStaticParams Instead</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/getstaticprops-and-getstaticpaths-are-no-longer-supported-in-the-next-js-app-router-use-generatestaticparams-instead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/getstaticprops-and-getstaticpaths-are-no-longer-supported-in-the-next-js-app-router-use-generatestaticparams-instead/</guid>
      <description>I was working on a Next.js 15 project using the App Router when I needed to handle dynamic routes. While reviewing an older project from GitHub, I noticed the use of getStaticProps and getStaticPaths to fetch and pre-render data.&#xA;However, when I tried implementing them in my project, I realized that these functions were not supported in the App Router. This left me confused about how to achieve the same functionality in the latest version of Next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling &#34;Property &#39;description&#39; is Possibly &#39;Undefined&#39;&#34; in TypeScript</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/handling-property-description-is-possibly-undefined-in-typescript/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/handling-property-description-is-possibly-undefined-in-typescript/</guid>
      <description>I was building a dynamic category page in Next.js where blog posts are displayed. Each post includes a title, image, categories, and a short description. However, when accessing the description property of a post object, I encountered the TypeScript error:&#xA;&#39;post.description&#39; is possibly &#39;undefined&#39;.&#xA;I realized this happened because TypeScript inferred that the description property might not always be defined for all post objects in the posts array. TypeScript, being strict about undefined properties, flagged this as a potential runtime issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix Emoji Rendering in MDX with remark-emoji in Next.js</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/fixing-emoji-rendering-in-mdx-with-remark-emoji-in-nextjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/fixing-emoji-rendering-in-mdx-with-remark-emoji-in-nextjs/</guid>
      <description>I moved my Hugo website to Next.js, but all the emojis I used with markdown syntax (e.g., :warning: or :bulb:) were displayed as text instead of actual emoji icons. I needed Next.js to recognize the emoji text like :bulb: in the MDX content and render it as an emoji icon.&#xA;How I Fixed the Issue Installed the Required Plugin&#xA;I searched online and found that I needed the remark-emoji plugin to handle emoji rendering in MDX files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix the date-fns format() Has No Default Export Error</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/fixing-date-fns-format-has-no-default-export-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/fixing-date-fns-format-has-no-default-export-error/</guid>
      <description>I was setting up the blog page for a website and needed to format the article&amp;rsquo;s date and updatedAt fields. I used this logic to determine whether to display the published or updated date:&#xA;{ blog.updatedAt === blog.date ? `Published on ${format(new Date(blog.date), &amp;#34;MMM dd, yyyy&amp;#34;)}` : `Updated on ${format(new Date(blog.updatedAt), &amp;#34;MMM dd, yyyy&amp;#34;)}`; } However, I noticed a squiggly line under the import statement for format. I had written:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating a Hugo Website from Netlify to Vercel: Resolving Deployment Errors Due to Hugo Version Mismatch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/migrating-hugo-website-netlify-to-vercel-version-mismatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/migrating-hugo-website-netlify-to-vercel-version-mismatch/</guid>
      <description>I recently decided to migrate my Hugo website from Netlify to Vercel to take advantage of Vercel&amp;rsquo;s features.&#xA;After cloning the project and removing any Netlify-specific configurations, I attempted to deploy the site on Vercel.&#xA;However, I encountered deployment errors because Vercel was using a different Hugo version than my local environment.&#xA;My local Hugo version was:&#xA;hugo v0.125.7-b1d808bc373f53ad37c8966bb02a6aea095db5f8 windows/amd64 BuildDate=2024-05-08T14:46:24Z VendorInfo=gohugoio To resolve this issue, I created a vercel.json file at the root of my project in Visual Studio Code (VSCode) with the following content:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolving the EPERM: Operation Not Permitted Error Caused by Concurrent Next.js Instances</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/resolving-the-eperm-operation-not-permitted-error-caused-by-concurrent-next-js-instances/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/resolving-the-eperm-operation-not-permitted-error-caused-by-concurrent-next-js-instances/</guid>
      <description>I was working on a Next.js 15 project using pnpm, and when I tried to run the build command (pnpm build), I encountered the following error:&#xA;uncaughtException [Error: EPERM: operation not permitted, open &amp;#39;C:\Users\USER\Desktop\My Projects\tooabstractive\.next\trace&amp;#39;] { errno: -4048, code: &amp;#39;EPERM&amp;#39;, syscall: &amp;#39;open&amp;#39;, path: &amp;#39;C:\\Users\\USER\\Desktop\\My Projects\\tooabstractive\\.next\\trace&amp;#39; } ELIFECYCLE Command failed with exit code 1. This error occurred because I was also running an instance of the app using pnpm dev (the development server) at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix TailwindCSS z-index Problem with `isolate`</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-tailwindcss-z-index-problem-with-isolate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-fix-tailwindcss-z-index-problem-with-isolate/</guid>
      <description>I was building a website with a sticky navbar that had a z-index of z-10. Later, I added a div with some text in the main content section.&#xA;When I scrolled up, I realized that the text appeared above the navbar, even though I had increased the navbar’s z-index and reduced the z-index of the content.&#xA;I even tried using the !important flag (e.g., !z-) on the z-index, which worked sometimes, but it felt messy and unreliable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Next.js 14 and 15 in Separate Branches and Deploy to Netlify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-use-next.js-14-and-15-in-separate-branches-and-deploy-to-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-use-next.js-14-and-15-in-separate-branches-and-deploy-to-netlify/</guid>
      <description>I deployed my project using Next.js 15 and React 19 (experimental).&#xA;While testing on Netlify, I noticed the blog posts on the site loaded slower compared to a project using Next.js 14.2.3.&#xA;I decided to revert to Next.js 14.2.3 for better performance but wanted to keep Next.js 15 on my GitHub in the main branch while working on the older version in a new branch.&#xA;How I Go About It Created a Branch for Next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Automatically Sort Tailwind CSS Classes in React or Next.js</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-automatically-sort-tailwind-css-classes-in-react-or-nextjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-automatically-sort-tailwind-css-classes-in-react-or-nextjs/</guid>
      <description>When using Tailwind CSS in a React or Next.js app, the order of classes in the className property doesn’t seem to matter for functionality.&#xA;However, I noticed it can get messy and inconsistent, especially for readability and maintaining a clean codebase. For instance:&#xA;&amp;lt;article className=&amp;#34;gap-3 rounded-lg border p-5 hover:bg-muted/60 flex&amp;#34;&amp;gt; {title} &amp;lt;/article&amp;gt; Even though this works fine, the classes are out of order and less readable.&#xA;To fix this issue, I used Prettier with a Tailwind CSS plugin to automatically sort my classes in a consistent order:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Add a Progress Bar to Your Next.js App for Better User Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/add-progress-bar-nextjs-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/add-progress-bar-nextjs-app/</guid>
      <description>I noticed that my Next.js blog post page took some time to load, which made the website feel unresponsive.&#xA;Even though I’ve been optimizing the app by dynamically importing modules, tracking large package sizes, and making improvements, it still felt sluggish to users.&#xA;To address this, I decided to add a progress bar at the top of the page.&#xA;Interestingly, it gives a sense of activity, reducing the perception of unresponsiveness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Unused Packages and Update Dependencies in a Next.js Project</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-unused-packages-and-update-dependencies-in-a-next-js-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/how-to-remove-unused-packages-and-update-dependencies-in-a-next-js-project/</guid>
      <description>The Problem I Faced: Losing Track of Unused Packages and Outdated Dependencies&#xA;I realized that my project was becoming difficult to manage due to a clutter of unused and outdated packages.&#xA;I had installed several packages, some of which I no longer needed, and others were out of date.&#xA;The issue arose because I was unsure which packages were actively being used in my code and which ones were just taking up space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Speed Up and Optimize Your Next.js Website or Blog for Faster Page Load</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/speed-up-optimize-nextjs-website-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-tech/speed-up-optimize-nextjs-website-blog/</guid>
      <description>In my previous post, I talked about improving the responsiveness of my Next.js website by adding a progress bar.&#xA;This helped by letting users know something was loading and made the site feel more responsive.&#xA;You can read about it here: How to Add a Progress Bar to Your Next.js App for Better User Experience.&#xA;However, while a progress bar can reduce bounce rates caused by perceived slowness, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t fix the actual speed of the site.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
