<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Productivity and guides on Tooabstractive</title>
    <link>/categories/productivity-and-guides/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Productivity and guides on Tooabstractive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/categories/productivity-and-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Payoff skills that every engineering students needs to learn before leaving college or University</title>
      <link>/misce-post/skills-every-engineering-student-needs-to-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/misce-post/skills-every-engineering-student-needs-to-learn/</guid>
      <description>This post is among the series of post tagged “4 years of college shouldn’t be a waste of time” wherewe discussed about how to be productive, have better grades and even develop skills that payoff onthe long run.Without doubt, we all know that engineering is an interesting but a complex field to study and mosttimes, it is due to the fact that the standard we are being taught with is quite outdated or notthat useful in the industry or the world we are in today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to study smart in engineering and have better grades without over stressing.</title>
      <link>/misce-post/how-to-study-better-in-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/misce-post/how-to-study-better-in-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Over the years of been an engineering student, I have met some good medical and engineering students.
And I have learned from them some tactics and strategies that help them study better and have good grades without over stressing.
Here in this post, I will be sharing most of them with you so you can fast track your engineering journey and make it fun.
Aim to study for many hours but split it into chunks We all know that engineering is not an easy field to study and you need lots and lots of time to study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 simple ways student can improve their writing skill</title>
      <link>/misce-post/simple-ways-student-can-improve-their-writing-skill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/misce-post/simple-ways-student-can-improve-their-writing-skill/</guid>
      <description>Being a student that loves to write and help others learn abstractive stuffs, I have been struggling a lot to improve my writing skill because it pays off a lot while in school and even out of school.
So in this post I will be sharing some of the most important ways (in no specific order) that can really help student improve their writing skill and in essence, become a better writer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple essay writing tips to help students write better essays and have good grades</title>
      <link>/misce-post/simple-essay-writing-tips-for-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/misce-post/simple-essay-writing-tips-for-student/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, writing an essay can be really intimidating due to lot of researches to be done and most likely at the end of writing the essay, it might even result in a bad grade which makes student sad or unhappy.
In this post I will be discussing some of the tips that can really impact your essay writing as a student because, to be frank am just a student like you and have been in your shoe too – which means this has most of the tips I have learnt along the way of me trying to write my own essay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to start reading books as a beginner (11 Tips on how to read 2 books a week)</title>
      <link>/misce-post/how-to-start-reading-books-as-a-beginner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/misce-post/how-to-start-reading-books-as-a-beginner/</guid>
      <description>Most people are frightened out and unmotivated when they hear people say I used to read three books a week or I read 100 books a year.
The truth of the matter is that yes most people are able to do so but in reality the way you think they read books is not actually how they do read and I have been in such state and was intrigued about it but at long last I was able to find my way through because even if I desire to read a fascinating book, I just get discourage over time as not all the pages or chapter will be interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Take Good Note in Class</title>
      <link>/misce-post/how-to-take-good-note-in-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/misce-post/how-to-take-good-note-in-class/</guid>
      <description>Taking good notes in class can not only enhance your study performance but also increase your academic points.
That’s why to take good notes is vital as a student because there are times whereby you write down some things in your note, studied it and understood it well but as exams approaches,
you get back to your note after some time and still you find it difficult to even understand what you wrote.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
