<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scholarship on Tooabstractive</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/scholarship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scholarship on Tooabstractive</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/scholarship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Michael Taiwo Scholarship: What Students Need to Know and How to Apply (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship-guide/michael-taiwo-scholarship-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship-guide/michael-taiwo-scholarship-guide/</guid>
      <description>The Michael Taiwo Scholarship primarily supports ambitious Nigerian students in pursuing graduate studies abroad.&#xA;It provides financial aid for standardized tests (GRE, GMAT, TOEFL, IELTS) and graduate school application fees, along with mentoring.&#xA;The scholarship also supports students from other countries, but to a lesser extent, such as Ghana, Pakistan, and Bangladesh, facilitating university education in the USA, UK, Canada, Europe, and Australia.&#xA;&amp;#x1f4a1; Keypoints for the 2024 Application</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Time to Submit a Scholarship Application: Tips for Success</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship-guide/what-is-the-best-time-to-submit-a-scholarship-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship-guide/what-is-the-best-time-to-submit-a-scholarship-application/</guid>
      <description>Securing a scholarship can be a game-changer for students. It not only provides financial relief but also opens doors to educational opportunities.&#xA;One of the most common questions students ask is whether submitting their scholarship application early or close to the deadline will impact their chances of securing the scholarship.&#xA;That&amp;rsquo;s what we will be answering in this post.&#xA;What is the Best Time to Submit a Scholarship Application? The answer to this question is that, it&amp;rsquo;s recommended to send your application well before the deadline to avoid any potential issues with submission or delays in processing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Organizations Offering GRE/GMAT/TOEFL/IELTS Scholarships in Nigeria</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship-guide/gre-gmat-toefl-ielts-scholarships-nigeria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship-guide/gre-gmat-toefl-ielts-scholarships-nigeria/</guid>
      <description>Are you a first-class or second-class upper graduate from a low-income background, motivated and highly talented? If so, there are organizations in Nigeria that can sponsor your GRE, GMAT, TOEFL, or IELTS fees, including your application fees.&#xA;These exams are crucial for securing fully funded international scholarships.&#xA;&amp;#x1f4a1; Understanding the Exams GRE (Graduate Record Examination): Required for many graduate school programs worldwide. TOEFL (Test of English as a Foreign Language) and IELTS (International English Language Testing System): Assess English proficiency for non-native speakers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
