<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>[&#34;Maths and Fun&#34;] on Tooabstractive</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/maths-and-fun/</link>
    <description>Recent content in [&#34;Maths and Fun&#34;] on Tooabstractive</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/maths-and-fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crammer&#39;s rule - the technique to simplify circuit analysis equations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/funmaths/what-is-crammers-rule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/funmaths/what-is-crammers-rule/</guid>
      <description>Solving simultaneous equations containing more than two variables&#xD;can be quite daunting if we use either elimination method or&#xD;substitution method because, thing gets a little bit complex. Also,&#xD;crammer&#39;s rule has been a technique used by engineers, students and by professors due to it compactibility and conciseness and lastly you can choose to use a calculator to help you solve that very fast.&#xD;Now back to business, variable names can be x and y or a and b or Ia&#xD;and Ib (as we do in circuit analysis for currents), it’s up to you&#xD;to choose what you want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> How to use a calculator to solve simultaneous equation fast - step by step</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/funmaths/how-to-solve-equation-using-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/funmaths/how-to-solve-equation-using-calculator/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we would solve a simultaneous equation in a very fast&#xD;and short time step by step using a Casio fx – 991MS as the&#xD;calculator to help us achieve our goal.&#xD;For example, let’s say our equation is [6x + 2y = 10] and [4x + y =&#xD;4] and we are to solve for the variables x and y.&#xD;Step 1 -&#xD;Switch on the calculator and then reset it, this is due to the fact&#xD;that sometimes we might have done some operation before which can&#xD;then alter our result for instance, if we put our calculator in&#xD;radian, the value is different from if it is in degree so therefore&#xD;always reset your calculator when starting off a new calculation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
