<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Signals and System on Tooabstractive</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Signals and System on Tooabstractive</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Signal and its Different Types In Electronics And Communications?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/what-is-a-signal-and-its-types/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/what-is-a-signal-and-its-types/</guid>
      <description>What is a signal? A signal is a function of an independent variable (e.g. of space, time, or density) that carries information representing a physical phenomenon.&#xA;So anything that carries information is considered a signal e.g.&#xA;The temperature of a room, Voltage and current in an electronic circuit Digital images, video, or audio Sounds or speeches etc. Position, speed, acceleration, or velocity of an object A stock market index The flow rate of fluid etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Solve Energy and Power Signals Problem Step By Step With Tips and Shortcuts?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/how-do-you-solve-energy-and-power-signals-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/how-do-you-solve-energy-and-power-signals-problem/</guid>
      <description>Before solving problems on energy and power signal, you need to understand what each of the signal means&#xA;What are power and energy signals? A power signals are signals with finite power while energy signals are signals with finite energy.&#xA;How do you solve energy and power signals? Here are the few things to remember in order to quickly identify if a signal is a power or an energy signal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Are the Basic Operations on Discrete Time Signals?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/what-are-the-basic-operations-on-discrete-time-signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/what-are-the-basic-operations-on-discrete-time-signals/</guid>
      <description>The following are the basic operations that can be done on discrete time signal&#xA;Addition Subtraction Multiplication Amplitude scaling Time shifting Time reversal Time scaling The first 4 operations are performed along the y or value axis while the last 3 are performed along the x or time axis.&#xA;but before solving problems on it, let’s discuss briefly on what discrete-time signal mean.&#xA;what is discrete-time signals or DTS? Discrete-time signals refers to signals that are defined only at discrete or finite time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between Power Signal and Energy Signal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/difference-between-power-signal-and-energy-signal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/difference-between-power-signal-and-energy-signal/</guid>
      <description>Power signals and energy signals are fundamental concepts in signal processing and are important for analyzing and characterizing different types of signals.&#xA;Read on: How Do You Solve Energy and Power Signals Problem Step By Step With Tips and Shortcuts?&#xA;In this article, we will look into the differences between these two signal categories and explore their unique properties.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Power Signals Energy Signals Distinguishing Average Power and Total Energy Key Differences between Power and Energy Signals 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are Dirichlet conditions for existence of Fourier series?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/dirichlet-conditions-for-existence-of-fourier-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/dirichlet-conditions-for-existence-of-fourier-series/</guid>
      <description>It is said that periodic signals can be analyzed using Fourier series, while non-periodic signals can be analyzed using Fourier transform.&#xA;But not all periodic signals will have a Fourier series expansion, hence here must be conditions a periodic signal have to meet for Fourier series to be used.&#xA;These conditions are defined by the mathematician Dirichlet, hence it is named Dirichlet conditions or the conditions for existence of Fourier series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differences Between Causal and Non-Causal Signal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/difference-between-causal-and-non-causal-signal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/difference-between-causal-and-non-causal-signal/</guid>
      <description>A signal can be defined as any physical quantity that carries information and varies with time, space, density, and other independent variable(s). It can also be defined as a pattern of variation in a physical quantity, such as sound or light, that can be measured and analyzed.&#xA;Signals can be classified into different categories or types based on various properties, such as the direction of the signal flow or the time-domain characteristics of the signal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Determine if a Signal Is Even or Odd?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/how-to-determine-if-a-signal-is-even-or-odd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/how-to-determine-if-a-signal-is-even-or-odd/</guid>
      <description>Knowing if a signal is an even or an odd signal is very important because it helps to simplify calculations and reduce the number of terms that need to be considered in a Fourier series or Fourier transform.&#xA;For example, when trying to find the Fourier analysis of a function, there are variables that need to be calculated, a0, an and bn where a0 is a constant value, an is the value associated with the even terms and bn is the value associated with the odd terms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Biomedical Signal Processing?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/what-is-biomedical-signal-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/what-is-biomedical-signal-processing/</guid>
      <description>Biomedical signal processing refers to the application of digital signal processing techniques to analyze and interpret physiological signals acquired from the human body.&#xA;These signals can originate from various sources, including electrocardiograms (ECGs), electroencephalograms (EEGs), and electromyograms (EMGs).&#xA;The primary objective of biomedical signal processing is to extract meaningful information from these signals, enabling healthcare professionals to diagnose and monitor patients effectively.&#xA;Biomedical signal processing involves the use of algorithms and mathematical techniques to manipulate, analyze, and interpret the acquired signals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between Linear Time Variant (LTV) and Linear Time Invariant (LTI) Systems</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/difference-between-linear-time-variant-and-linear-time-invariant-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/difference-between-linear-time-variant-and-linear-time-invariant-system/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will look at the main difference between linear time variant (LTV) and linear time invariant (LTI) systems.&#xA;We will discuss their definitions, characteristics, and applications to gain a comprehensive understanding of their functionalities and distinctions.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;What are LTV Systems? What are LTI Systems? Differences between LTV and LTI Systems 1. Dependence on Input Time 2. Memory and Environmental Influence 3. Performance and Complexity Applications of LTV Systems Applications of LTI Systems Additional Properties of LTV and LTI Systems 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Check Whether a System Is LTI or Not?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/how-do-you-check-whether-a-system-is-lti-or-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/how-do-you-check-whether-a-system-is-lti-or-not/</guid>
      <description>To analyze the response and stability of a system, it is important to determine whether it is LTI or not.&#xA;The LTI property helps us understand how a system behaves when subjected to different inputs.&#xA;By performing specific tests, we can determine whether a system exhibits the desired LTI characteristics.&#xA;Table of Contents ↬&#xD;Linearity Test Time Invariance Test Examples of LTI Systems 1. RC Filter 2. RLC Filter 3. PID Controller Examples of Non-LTI Systems 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are Deterministic and Random Signals? with Examples and Differences</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/deterministic-and-random-signals-with-examples-and-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/signal-and-system/deterministic-and-random-signals-with-examples-and-differences/</guid>
      <description>Signals are all around us, carrying information in various forms. A signal is a function that carries information about a physical phenomenon.&#xA;It varies with an independent variable, such as space, time, or density.&#xA;In essence, anything that conveys information can be considered a signal. Examples include: temperature of a room, voltage, and current in an electronic circuit, digital images, video, or audio etc.&#xA;We can broadly categorize signals into two types: deterministic and random signals.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
